[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "title": "Level 1 \u2014 Starters",
    "timeLimit": 140,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 0,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "k",
            "e",
            "h",
            "y",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "s",
            "j",
            "b",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "l",
            "f",
            "d",
            "o",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "s",
            "t",
            "d",
            "t",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "l",
            "r",
            "r",
            "h",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "p",
            "p",
            "a",
            "h",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I show up with a smile when you feel good inside.",
        "answer": "happy"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 8,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "k",
            "t",
            "e",
            "n",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "p",
            "o",
            "o",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "o",
            "n",
            "s",
            "s",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "a",
            "l",
            "o",
            "o",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "r",
            "h",
            "d",
            "p",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "g",
            "a",
            "e",
            "o",
            "y"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I make you shiver and wear a jacket.",
        "answer": "cold"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 6,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "y",
            "i",
            "n",
            "l",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "a",
            "t",
            "d",
            "r",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "e",
            "y",
            "u",
            "o",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "r",
            "d",
            "t",
            "c",
            "w"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "c",
            "d",
            "c",
            "a",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "e",
            "a",
            "n",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I purr, chase mice, and love to nap in the sun.",
        "answer": "cat"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 6,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "f",
            "a",
            "a",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "c",
            "t",
            "e",
            "n",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "o",
            "a",
            "s",
            "r",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "i",
            "s",
            "u",
            "o",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "r",
            "n",
            "i",
            "w",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "l",
            "m",
            "v",
            "s",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I'm faster than walking; you do me in races.",
        "answer": "run"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 6,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "h",
            "s",
            "n",
            "t",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "a",
            "u",
            "w",
            "w",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "s",
            "m",
            "d",
            "o",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "w",
            "n",
            "s",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "r",
            "s",
            "p",
            "o",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "o",
            "e",
            "e",
            "c"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I light up the day and keep the Earth warm.",
        "answer": "sun"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 8,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "a",
            "h",
            "r",
            "c",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "e",
            "v",
            "h",
            "l",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "o",
            "i",
            "u",
            "d",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "a",
            "e",
            "m",
            "q",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "o",
            "t",
            "d",
            "w",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "s",
            "r",
            "i",
            "h",
            "m"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I'm a color, like the sky or the ocean.",
        "answer": "blue"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 8,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "b",
            "e",
            "m",
            "t",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "g",
            "a",
            "h",
            "g",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "s",
            "r",
            "l",
            "g",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "t",
            "e",
            "n",
            "l",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "a",
            "m",
            "a",
            "y",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "b",
            "n",
            "n",
            "a",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I'm round and fun to kick, throw, or bounce.",
        "answer": "ball"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 9,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "l",
            "n",
            "l",
            "g",
            "z"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "o",
            "i",
            "l",
            "v",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "d",
            "r",
            "y",
            "t",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "j",
            "u",
            "m",
            "p",
            "j",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "t",
            "e",
            "w",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "i",
            "r",
            "e",
            "e",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I go up off the ground with both feet.",
        "answer": "jump"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 6,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "r",
            "i",
            "e",
            "r",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "m",
            "m",
            "e",
            "l",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "o",
            "i",
            "o",
            "z"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "a",
            "t",
            "o",
            "s",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "e",
            "o",
            "a",
            "s",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "l",
            "n",
            "n",
            "e",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You do this with food, three times a day.",
        "answer": "eat"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "d",
            "i",
            "r",
            "a",
            "z"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "a",
            "i",
            "r",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "u",
            "d",
            "a",
            "o",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "a",
            "i",
            "h",
            "j",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "m",
            "t",
            "c",
            "o",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "i",
            "m",
            "e",
            "e",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You sit on me to rest your legs. I have four legs.",
        "answer": "chair"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "title": "Level 2 \u2014 Everyday",
    "timeLimit": 130,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 69,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "h",
            "h",
            "a",
            "a",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "y",
            "t",
            "o",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "u",
            "t",
            "o",
            "r",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "a",
            "k",
            "e",
            "n",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "o",
            "r",
            "v",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "a",
            "k",
            "c",
            "i",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have pages and words \u2014 you read me for fun or facts.",
        "answer": "book"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 8,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "e",
            "m",
            "r",
            "t",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "i",
            "b",
            "l",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "r",
            "l",
            "s",
            "t",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "a",
            "k",
            "b",
            "t",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "a",
            "t",
            "o",
            "r",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "t",
            "r",
            "d",
            "h",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I'm white, cold, and come from cows.",
        "answer": "milk"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 8,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "e",
            "h",
            "e",
            "t",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "a",
            "e",
            "e",
            "c",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "u",
            "r",
            "r",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "y",
            "a",
            "t",
            "t",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "h",
            "p",
            "b",
            "x",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "p",
            "s",
            "s",
            "y",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have roots, a trunk, and leaves \u2014 I give shade.",
        "answer": "tree"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 9,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "t",
            "o",
            "i",
            "a",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "r",
            "l",
            "u",
            "e",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "a",
            "t",
            "l",
            "n",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "t",
            "i",
            "f",
            "i",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "m",
            "p",
            "x",
            "y",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "c",
            "l",
            "a",
            "a",
            "m"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I curve your lips upward when you're happy.",
        "answer": "smile"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "b",
            "r",
            "a",
            "v",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "r",
            "a",
            "m",
            "e",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "a",
            "i",
            "c",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "m",
            "h",
            "h",
            "r",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "n",
            "a",
            "j",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "d",
            "e",
            "p",
            "h",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I face danger without fear \u2014 like a firefighter or hero.",
        "answer": "brave"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 8,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "u",
            "a",
            "x",
            "l",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "d",
            "r",
            "i",
            "n",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "n",
            "a",
            "i",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "y",
            "m",
            "i",
            "p",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "m",
            "c",
            "d",
            "k",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "n",
            "l",
            "h",
            "f",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I show care and help others feel good.",
        "answer": "kind"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 9,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "t",
            "i",
            "a",
            "p",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "e",
            "i",
            "s",
            "u",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "i",
            "n",
            "n",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "i",
            "h",
            "o",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "s",
            "u",
            "l",
            "i",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "d",
            "l",
            "o",
            "i",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I come with joy, often with a big sound.",
        "answer": "laugh"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 11,
        "grid": [
          [
            "c",
            "a",
            "m",
            "h",
            "b",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "a",
            "h",
            "r",
            "g",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "a",
            "t",
            "p",
            "e",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "p",
            "t",
            "c",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "e",
            "b",
            "h",
            "h",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "f",
            "m",
            "t",
            "u",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You do this to a ball or falling object with your hands.",
        "answer": "catch"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "j",
            "n",
            "i",
            "c",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "d",
            "i",
            "l",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "m",
            "l",
            "d",
            "c",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "c",
            "t",
            "i",
            "c",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "c",
            "r",
            "u",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "w",
            "o",
            "s",
            "l",
            "b"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You do this with blocks or bricks to make something tall.",
        "answer": "build"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 8,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "y",
            "n",
            "o",
            "o",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "k",
            "n",
            "n",
            "t",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "c",
            "u",
            "t",
            "l",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "o",
            "o",
            "a",
            "d",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "h",
            "s",
            "a",
            "w",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "u",
            "n",
            "s",
            "m",
            "y"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You do this with soap and water to get clean.",
        "answer": "wash"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "title": "Level 3 \u2014 Discovery",
    "timeLimit": 120,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 154,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "r",
            "t",
            "t",
            "o",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "n",
            "o",
            "t",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "h",
            "l",
            "o",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "b",
            "p",
            "u",
            "g",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "p",
            "l",
            "r",
            "k",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "r",
            "e",
            "v",
            "i",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I flow down to the ocean and fish swim in me.",
        "answer": "river"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "f",
            "r",
            "c",
            "l",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "a",
            "k",
            "r",
            "r",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "p",
            "m",
            "o",
            "n",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "p",
            "n",
            "d",
            "f",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "l",
            "i",
            "s",
            "o",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "r",
            "i",
            "r",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am red or green, crunchy, and grow on trees.",
        "answer": "apple"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "y",
            "r",
            "m",
            "p",
            "g",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "c",
            "e",
            "l",
            "o",
            "w"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "l",
            "s",
            "e",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "a",
            "e",
            "o",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "w",
            "o",
            "t",
            "c",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "l",
            "s",
            "a",
            "t",
            "k"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have a face and hands but no body; I tell time.",
        "answer": "clock"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "l",
            "v",
            "r",
            "y",
            "s",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "o",
            "e",
            "a",
            "a",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "k",
            "g",
            "h",
            "q",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "e",
            "i",
            "t",
            "v",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "v",
            "t",
            "m",
            "a",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "d",
            "h",
            "d",
            "o",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am a big cat with orange fur and black stripes.",
        "answer": "tiger"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 8,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "e",
            "w",
            "s",
            "d",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "h",
            "o",
            "r",
            "e",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "i",
            "e",
            "s",
            "n",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "a",
            "m",
            "g",
            "d",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "a",
            "o",
            "n",
            "t",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "o",
            "m",
            "h",
            "a",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You do this in your sleep when your eyes are closed.",
        "answer": "dream"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "l",
            "p",
            "e",
            "d",
            "o",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "i",
            "l",
            "e",
            "o",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "t",
            "l",
            "e",
            "s",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "f",
            "t",
            "u",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "h",
            "o",
            "a",
            "r",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "h",
            "r",
            "t",
            "n",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have a roof and walls; you live inside me.",
        "answer": "house"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 8,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "t",
            "m",
            "e",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "u",
            "y",
            "l",
            "o",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "s",
            "n",
            "n",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "e",
            "e",
            "e",
            "r",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "n",
            "p",
            "m",
            "h",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "r",
            "e",
            "t",
            "g",
            "m"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I shine at night and change my shape in the sky.",
        "answer": "moon"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "t",
            "t",
            "l",
            "p",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "s",
            "e",
            "z",
            "t",
            "q"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "e",
            "f",
            "s",
            "n",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "r",
            "o",
            "i",
            "y",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "u",
            "e",
            "h",
            "w",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "v",
            "n",
            "c",
            "s",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You wear these on your feet before going outside.",
        "answer": "shoes"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "a",
            "o",
            "e",
            "c",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "l",
            "e",
            "t",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "v",
            "n",
            "r",
            "e",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "n",
            "o",
            "w",
            "s",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "l",
            "g",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "i",
            "x",
            "b",
            "s",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am a large bird that flies high and hunts.",
        "answer": "eagle"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 8,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "p",
            "o",
            "n",
            "g",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "e",
            "l",
            "b",
            "p",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "f",
            "h",
            "t",
            "e",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "t",
            "a",
            "h",
            "t",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "o",
            "e",
            "s",
            "h",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "s",
            "s",
            "a",
            "r",
            "g"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am green, cover the ground, and cows eat me.",
        "answer": "grass"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "title": "Level 4 \u2014 Challenge",
    "timeLimit": 110,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 244,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "t",
            "n",
            "e",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "w",
            "n",
            "e",
            "i",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "a",
            "r",
            "a",
            "s",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "t",
            "s",
            "n",
            "b",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "e",
            "e",
            "f",
            "n",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "c",
            "e",
            "g",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am clear, I have no taste, and you drink me.",
        "answer": "water"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 8,
        "grid": [
          [
            "d",
            "t",
            "o",
            "l",
            "n",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "m",
            "s",
            "e",
            "y",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "h",
            "n",
            "l",
            "s",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "e",
            "a",
            "m",
            "g",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "o",
            "r",
            "c",
            "y",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "u",
            "i",
            "e",
            "a",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You use us to see the world around you.",
        "answer": "eyes"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "c",
            "e",
            "g",
            "e",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "s",
            "c",
            "n",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "u",
            "t",
            "a",
            "c",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "n",
            "i",
            "r",
            "s",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "l",
            "t",
            "a",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "u",
            "v",
            "o",
            "h",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I carry my house on my back and move very slowly.",
        "answer": "snail"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 9,
        "grid": [
          [
            "m",
            "i",
            "e",
            "a",
            "f",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "w",
            "r",
            "i",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "l",
            "s",
            "a",
            "d",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "r",
            "r",
            "a",
            "r",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "g",
            "v",
            "n",
            "s",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "l",
            "n",
            "h",
            "o",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I fall from the clouds and make puddles.",
        "answer": "rain"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "d",
            "r",
            "l",
            "a",
            "u",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "h",
            "t",
            "b",
            "s",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "w",
            "r",
            "a",
            "t",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "a",
            "r",
            "e",
            "t",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "h",
            "h",
            "n",
            "s",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "h",
            "h",
            "i",
            "e",
            "p"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I come from wood and you write on me.",
        "answer": "paper"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 11,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "b",
            "c",
            "w",
            "l",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "t",
            "g",
            "r",
            "r",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "c",
            "n",
            "l",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "e",
            "n",
            "s",
            "e",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "d",
            "h",
            "o",
            "t",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "e",
            "n",
            "h",
            "d"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am sweet, sticky, and made by bees.",
        "answer": "honey"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "h",
            "e",
            "s",
            "k",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "n",
            "i",
            "a",
            "r",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "o",
            "d",
            "s",
            "p",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "r",
            "r",
            "a",
            "i",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "u",
            "l",
            "e",
            "e",
            "x"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "d",
            "v",
            "r",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I run on tracks and have a whistle.",
        "answer": "train"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 8,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "r",
            "k",
            "s",
            "e",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "m",
            "i",
            "n",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "h",
            "o",
            "s",
            "w",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "f",
            "r",
            "t",
            "b",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "e",
            "o",
            "t",
            "e",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "h",
            "e",
            "a",
            "d",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You lie on me at night with a pillow.",
        "answer": "bed"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "w",
            "t",
            "n",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "i",
            "e",
            "b",
            "n",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "g",
            "r",
            "x",
            "o",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "h",
            "n",
            "r",
            "m",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "s",
            "a",
            "t",
            "e",
            "w"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "r",
            "t",
            "l",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am yellow, sour, and shaped like a football.",
        "answer": "lemon"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "p",
            "e",
            "m",
            "i",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "r",
            "e",
            "e",
            "n",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "t",
            "r",
            "s",
            "a",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "u",
            "c",
            "a",
            "y",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "b",
            "p",
            "n",
            "t",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "i",
            "h",
            "h",
            "o",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Mixing blue and yellow paint makes this color.",
        "answer": "green"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "title": "Level 5 \u2014 Expert",
    "timeLimit": 100,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 336,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "h",
            "n",
            "i",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "e",
            "h",
            "e",
            "h",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "o",
            "n",
            "a",
            "n",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "r",
            "a",
            "a",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "i",
            "n",
            "e",
            "l",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "r",
            "d",
            "e",
            "a",
            "p"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Earth, Mars, and Venus are examples of this.",
        "answer": "planet"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "a",
            "a",
            "m",
            "r",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "r",
            "c",
            "a",
            "h",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "m",
            "a",
            "o",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "n",
            "o",
            "o",
            "o",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "s",
            "a",
            "o",
            "e",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "e",
            "d",
            "i",
            "p",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have eight legs and spin a sticky web.",
        "answer": "spider"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "u",
            "o",
            "m",
            "e",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "v",
            "h",
            "c",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "b",
            "n",
            "c",
            "t",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "a",
            "f",
            "l",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "i",
            "y",
            "l",
            "y",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "v",
            "n",
            "a",
            "y"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You move your body to the rhythm of music.",
        "answer": "dance"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "e",
            "s",
            "o",
            "d",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "t",
            "r",
            "p",
            "i",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "r",
            "d",
            "i",
            "w",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "z",
            "c",
            "a",
            "z",
            "a",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "r",
            "h",
            "z",
            "f",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "n",
            "i",
            "a",
            "h",
            "c"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am round, cheesy, and sliced into triangles.",
        "answer": "pizza"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "h",
            "f",
            "a",
            "a",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "s",
            "a",
            "t",
            "i",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "e",
            "g",
            "c",
            "x",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "n",
            "i",
            "d",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "x",
            "e",
            "i",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "r",
            "t",
            "d",
            "f",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have lead inside and an eraser on top.",
        "answer": "pencil"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "a",
            "h",
            "o",
            "o",
            "w"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "a",
            "d",
            "e",
            "s",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "d",
            "y",
            "e",
            "o",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "u",
            "a",
            "l",
            "n",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "s",
            "m",
            "n",
            "n",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "e",
            "a",
            "r",
            "t",
            "m"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I pump blood inside your chest.",
        "answer": "heart"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "n",
            "s",
            "i",
            "c",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "t",
            "t",
            "h",
            "t",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "t",
            "l",
            "u",
            "t",
            "w"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "r",
            "o",
            "r",
            "o",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "t",
            "p",
            "r",
            "l",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "t",
            "o",
            "m",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I bring thunder, lightning, and heavy rain.",
        "answer": "storm"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 8,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "b",
            "v",
            "a",
            "e",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "t",
            "e",
            "a",
            "f",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "n",
            "s",
            "a",
            "t",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "a",
            "d",
            "j",
            "c",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "n",
            "u",
            "o",
            "e",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "t",
            "r",
            "r",
            "o",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A place with sand and ocean where you swim.",
        "answer": "beach"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "d",
            "r",
            "s",
            "u",
            "m",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "r",
            "c",
            "u",
            "i",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "p",
            "s",
            "l",
            "a",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "i",
            "r",
            "r",
            "h",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "o",
            "s",
            "n",
            "r",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "s",
            "n",
            "g",
            "c",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Songs, melodies, and tunes are all called this.",
        "answer": "music"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 8,
        "grid": [
          [
            "b",
            "i",
            "n",
            "n",
            "n",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "n",
            "a",
            "c",
            "m",
            "w"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "h",
            "f",
            "u",
            "k",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "e",
            "i",
            "h",
            "l",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "r",
            "s",
            "t",
            "t",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "a",
            "e",
            "e",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The color of snow, milk, and clouds.",
        "answer": "white"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "title": "Level 6 \u2014 Master",
    "timeLimit": 90,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 428,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "v",
            "s",
            "v",
            "f",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "t",
            "h",
            "r",
            "o",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "a",
            "a",
            "n",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "l",
            "e",
            "e",
            "p",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "o",
            "l",
            "t",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "z",
            "r",
            "t",
            "u",
            "m",
            "c"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am what you do in a bed at night to rest.",
        "answer": "sleep"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "f",
            "k",
            "e",
            "h",
            "t",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "l",
            "a",
            "w",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "i",
            "o",
            "p",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "s",
            "h",
            "w",
            "f",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "e",
            "h",
            "w",
            "e",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "i",
            "s",
            "u",
            "a",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am colorful, smell nice, and bees love me.",
        "answer": "flower"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "b",
            "i",
            "i",
            "a",
            "d",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "r",
            "n",
            "y",
            "r",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "u",
            "a",
            "b",
            "g",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "e",
            "r",
            "i",
            "r",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "s",
            "a",
            "u",
            "n",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "s",
            "a",
            "h",
            "m",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am inside your head and help you think.",
        "answer": "brain"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "v",
            "w",
            "w",
            "d",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "l",
            "i",
            "o",
            "s",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "o",
            "t",
            "l",
            "s",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "i",
            "a",
            "n",
            "t",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "n",
            "l",
            "o",
            "r",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "i",
            "p",
            "r",
            "e",
            "l"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am land surrounded by water on all sides.",
        "answer": "island"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "d",
            "a",
            "e",
            "r",
            "b",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "a",
            "t",
            "u",
            "p",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "v",
            "q",
            "e",
            "i",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "l",
            "i",
            "o",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "i",
            "h",
            "o",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "s",
            "n",
            "n",
            "e",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You make sandwiches with two slices of me.",
        "answer": "bread"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "m",
            "c",
            "t",
            "u",
            "i",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "a",
            "a",
            "t",
            "x"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "t",
            "n",
            "s",
            "e",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "d",
            "c",
            "k",
            "a",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "l",
            "r",
            "a",
            "e",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "h",
            "t",
            "d",
            "o",
            "y"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I love bananas, climb trees, and have a tail.",
        "answer": "monkey"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "x",
            "e",
            "m",
            "c",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "w",
            "a",
            "i",
            "e",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "e",
            "s",
            "r",
            "p",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "l",
            "r",
            "r",
            "i",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "h",
            "k",
            "o",
            "i",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "e",
            "o",
            "r",
            "f",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Look at me to see your own face.",
        "answer": "mirror"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "r",
            "m",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "l",
            "t",
            "s",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "a",
            "s",
            "c",
            "b",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "o",
            "d",
            "f",
            "r",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "o",
            "a",
            "w",
            "c",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "u",
            "r",
            "s",
            "d",
            "v"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You use this to speak or sing songs.",
        "answer": "voice"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "a",
            "h",
            "a",
            "t",
            "q"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "e",
            "e",
            "n",
            "s",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "t",
            "d",
            "o",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "d",
            "t",
            "n",
            "r",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "c",
            "u",
            "i",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "f",
            "n",
            "n",
            "f",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A large place filled with many trees and animals.",
        "answer": "forest"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "b",
            "d",
            "u",
            "y",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "k",
            "e",
            "n",
            "a",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "e",
            "c",
            "y",
            "i",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "d",
            "n",
            "u",
            "r",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "e",
            "s",
            "t",
            "n",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "c",
            "l",
            "o",
            "u",
            "d"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I float in the sky and look like cotton.",
        "answer": "cloud"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "title": "Level 6 \u2014 Master",
    "timeLimit": 90,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 534,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "o",
            "h",
            "y",
            "h",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "i",
            "y",
            "e",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "e",
            "e",
            "r",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "a",
            "t",
            "c",
            "c",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "o",
            "d",
            "a",
            "h",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "r",
            "a",
            "o",
            "g",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I follow you on a sunny day but disappear in the dark.",
        "answer": "shadow"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "f",
            "t",
            "t",
            "e",
            "u",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "i",
            "r",
            "o",
            "g",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "a",
            "d",
            "a",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "a",
            "i",
            "d",
            "s",
            "w"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "r",
            "d",
            "f",
            "f",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "h",
            "t",
            "w",
            "o",
            "u"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I help you cross over a river or a road.",
        "answer": "bridge"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "a",
            "k",
            "o",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "r",
            "r",
            "l",
            "r",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "y",
            "e",
            "b",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "t",
            "m",
            "i",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "a",
            "i",
            "w",
            "n",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "a",
            "a",
            "i",
            "l",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You use me to take photographs.",
        "answer": "camera"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "e",
            "i",
            "a",
            "a",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "e",
            "n",
            "t",
            "n",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "s",
            "t",
            "n",
            "u",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "r",
            "e",
            "n",
            "l",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "b",
            "s",
            "p",
            "i",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "s",
            "w",
            "h",
            "x",
            "w"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The coldest season of the year, when it might snow.",
        "answer": "winter"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "u",
            "t",
            "a",
            "d",
            "r",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "s",
            "c",
            "g",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "t",
            "p",
            "t",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "a",
            "i",
            "r",
            "d",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "o",
            "c",
            "k",
            "e",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "f",
            "o",
            "c",
            "e",
            "l"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I fly very fast into space to reach the moon.",
        "answer": "rocket"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "t",
            "r",
            "s",
            "f",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "h",
            "e",
            "i",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "r",
            "t",
            "n",
            "f",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "f",
            "n",
            "c",
            "i",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "u",
            "a",
            "o",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "e",
            "r",
            "l",
            "h",
            "d"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I help sick people get better.",
        "answer": "doctor"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "w",
            "m",
            "t",
            "e",
            "r",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "d",
            "e",
            "e",
            "r",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "m",
            "o",
            "n",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "i",
            "r",
            "s",
            "a",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "h",
            "s",
            "u",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "g",
            "t",
            "t",
            "t",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The color of the sun, lemons, and bananas.",
        "answer": "yellow"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 10,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "p",
            "o",
            "n",
            "s",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "f",
            "h",
            "o",
            "y",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "u",
            "r",
            "g",
            "e",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "s",
            "i",
            "s",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "i",
            "h",
            "r",
            "g",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "i",
            "g",
            "a",
            "n",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You have five of these on each hand.",
        "answer": "finger"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "t",
            "g",
            "h",
            "c",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "h",
            "e",
            "d",
            "o",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "s",
            "s",
            "d",
            "p",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "f",
            "t",
            "l",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "i",
            "l",
            "e",
            "t",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "i",
            "r",
            "c",
            "l",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A round shape like a ring or a ball.",
        "answer": "circle"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "l",
            "m",
            "a",
            "d",
            "c",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "l",
            "f",
            "l",
            "a",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "t",
            "o",
            "n",
            "k",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "c",
            "h",
            "o",
            "o",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "e",
            "k",
            "g",
            "d",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "u",
            "t",
            "i",
            "o",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The place children go to learn and study.",
        "answer": "school"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "title": "Level 7 \u2014 Little More Harder",
    "timeLimit": 85,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 648,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "n",
            "t",
            "t",
            "s",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "e",
            "e",
            "s",
            "t",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "a",
            "c",
            "h",
            "e",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "n",
            "a",
            "a",
            "o",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "d",
            "t",
            "u",
            "p",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "e",
            "i",
            "i",
            "d",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The empty place between stars and planets.",
        "answer": "space"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "o",
            "l",
            "d",
            "t",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "t",
            "s",
            "s",
            "e",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "s",
            "o",
            "f",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "r",
            "i",
            "r",
            "e",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "u",
            "g",
            "e",
            "m",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "h",
            "n",
            "t",
            "n",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I bring heavy rain, thunder, and lightning.",
        "answer": "storm"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "s",
            "c",
            "l",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "a",
            "n",
            "n",
            "t",
            "q"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "o",
            "d",
            "r",
            "t",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "w",
            "o",
            "t",
            "d",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "n",
            "o",
            "t",
            "e",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "l",
            "o",
            "r",
            "o",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "This direction is the opposite of South.",
        "answer": "north"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "t",
            "n",
            "a",
            "l",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "i",
            "l",
            "i",
            "t",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "z",
            "t",
            "n",
            "e",
            "n",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "a",
            "r",
            "e",
            "d",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "t",
            "e",
            "p",
            "l",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "u",
            "a",
            "r",
            "r",
            "m"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have leaves, a stem, and I grow from the ground.",
        "answer": "plant"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "m",
            "a",
            "e",
            "d",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "a",
            "r",
            "o",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "i",
            "p",
            "g",
            "i",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "a",
            "s",
            "e",
            "i",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "s",
            "f",
            "u",
            "n",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "i",
            "f",
            "n",
            "a",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A trick used by magicians to amaze people.",
        "answer": "magic"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "o",
            "o",
            "r",
            "n",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "u",
            "a",
            "i",
            "h",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "s",
            "e",
            "o",
            "d",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "e",
            "u",
            "e",
            "w",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "r",
            "a",
            "r",
            "s",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "i",
            "v",
            "o",
            "b",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You use this to clean your teeth.",
        "answer": "brush"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "w",
            "l",
            "f",
            "h",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "h",
            "l",
            "t",
            "t",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "n",
            "c",
            "t",
            "m",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "e",
            "o",
            "n",
            "m",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "i",
            "t",
            "s",
            "u",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "m",
            "t",
            "r",
            "m",
            "l"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "We eat this meal in the middle of the day.",
        "answer": "lunch"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "o",
            "b",
            "o",
            "t",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "g",
            "r",
            "d",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "u",
            "a",
            "t",
            "o",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "j",
            "r",
            "h",
            "k",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "t",
            "w",
            "t",
            "i",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "r",
            "l",
            "d",
            "t",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A machine that can move and do work like a human.",
        "answer": "robot"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "d",
            "o",
            "d",
            "o",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "d",
            "g",
            "g",
            "e",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "c",
            "v",
            "e",
            "h",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "l",
            "o",
            "c",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "x",
            "e",
            "s",
            "o",
            "o",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "t",
            "e",
            "t",
            "u",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am white, float in the air, and disappear.",
        "answer": "ghost"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "y",
            "n",
            "s",
            "l",
            "p",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "n",
            "f",
            "r",
            "e",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "i",
            "s",
            "n",
            "s",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "g",
            "h",
            "t",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "r",
            "i",
            "h",
            "u",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "f",
            "o",
            "s",
            "t",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The time when the sun is down and the moon is up.",
        "answer": "night"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "title": "Level 8 \u2014 Harder",
    "timeLimit": 80,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 766,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "l",
            "d",
            "n",
            "o",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "n",
            "a",
            "d",
            "n",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "o",
            "i",
            "a",
            "f",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "a",
            "b",
            "s",
            "c",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "g",
            "a",
            "r",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "n",
            "y",
            "e",
            "i",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I breathe fire, fly, and have scales.",
        "answer": "dragon"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "e",
            "t",
            "r",
            "n",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "n",
            "a",
            "r",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "n",
            "e",
            "e",
            "s",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "c",
            "k",
            "c",
            "d",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "h",
            "t",
            "f",
            "r",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "a",
            "k",
            "e",
            "h",
            "f"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A very large body of salt water.",
        "answer": "ocean"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "n",
            "c",
            "o",
            "o",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "h",
            "t",
            "k",
            "t",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "g",
            "o",
            "o",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "b",
            "i",
            "t",
            "a",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "f",
            "s",
            "r",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "e",
            "t",
            "e",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A loud sound that might hurt your ears.",
        "answer": "noise"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "s",
            "h",
            "a",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "i",
            "t",
            "f",
            "r",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "t",
            "r",
            "r",
            "p",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "i",
            "o",
            "u",
            "d",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "r",
            "i",
            "i",
            "m",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "u",
            "l",
            "t",
            "o",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Apples, bananas, and oranges are types of this.",
        "answer": "fruit"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "s",
            "i",
            "t",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "q",
            "f",
            "s",
            "o",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "u",
            "a",
            "c",
            "i",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "i",
            "n",
            "m",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "e",
            "l",
            "d",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "t",
            "s",
            "s",
            "i",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The opposite of loud; when there is silence.",
        "answer": "quiet"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "n",
            "u",
            "a",
            "a",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "e",
            "e",
            "i",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "n",
            "e",
            "o",
            "f",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "z",
            "e",
            "b",
            "r",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "i",
            "o",
            "e",
            "r",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "g",
            "r",
            "a",
            "e",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I look like a horse but have black and white stripes.",
        "answer": "zebra"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "g",
            "m",
            "a",
            "r",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "e",
            "i",
            "t",
            "t",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "p",
            "i",
            "r",
            "h",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "u",
            "a",
            "f",
            "l",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "p",
            "e",
            "p",
            "n",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "t",
            "u",
            "a",
            "n",
            "c"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A fun celebration with cake, music, and balloons.",
        "answer": "party"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "u",
            "t",
            "l",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "x",
            "o",
            "w",
            "h",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "n",
            "i",
            "h",
            "q",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "n",
            "s",
            "l",
            "i",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "u",
            "g",
            "a",
            "r",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "o",
            "t",
            "s",
            "k",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am white, sweet, and used to bake cakes.",
        "answer": "sugar"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "e",
            "t",
            "c",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "i",
            "s",
            "a",
            "r",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "l",
            "r",
            "s",
            "u",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "m",
            "u",
            "r",
            "n",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "a",
            "n",
            "a",
            "e",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "e",
            "e",
            "f",
            "v",
            "f"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I work in a hospital and help the doctor.",
        "answer": "nurse"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "f",
            "e",
            "a",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "a",
            "n",
            "r",
            "d",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "u",
            "a",
            "h",
            "w",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "w",
            "l",
            "s",
            "o",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "e",
            "p",
            "e",
            "r",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "c",
            "a",
            "i",
            "p",
            "m"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have wings and engines to fly in the sky.",
        "answer": "plane"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "title": "Level 9 \u2014 Expert Harder",
    "timeLimit": 75,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 888,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "o",
            "r",
            "s",
            "b",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "i",
            "d",
            "l",
            "u",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "o",
            "l",
            "c",
            "c",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "e",
            "a",
            "y",
            "n",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "i",
            "e",
            "r",
            "r",
            "j"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "d",
            "e",
            "t",
            "a",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A large vehicle used to carry heavy loads.",
        "answer": "truck"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "l",
            "r",
            "h",
            "r",
            "p",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "h",
            "e",
            "a",
            "a",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "o",
            "t",
            "h",
            "h",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "s",
            "b",
            "a",
            "g",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "u",
            "f",
            "s",
            "a",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "r",
            "t",
            "h",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The planet we live on.",
        "answer": "earth"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "c",
            "r",
            "e",
            "o",
            "l",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "d",
            "m",
            "d",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "t",
            "l",
            "h",
            "n",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "p",
            "t",
            "b",
            "o",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "t",
            "n",
            "t",
            "a",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "l",
            "o",
            "r",
            "r",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Furniture with four legs where you eat meals.",
        "answer": "table"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "u",
            "o",
            "u",
            "i",
            "f",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "s",
            "c",
            "d",
            "r",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "o",
            "m",
            "a",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "l",
            "d",
            "d",
            "o",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "p",
            "o",
            "o",
            "n",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "s",
            "u",
            "b",
            "s",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You use this utensil to eat soup or cereal.",
        "answer": "spoon"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "c",
            "t",
            "e",
            "e",
            "d",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "r",
            "g",
            "s",
            "t",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "e",
            "o",
            "u",
            "s",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "y",
            "p",
            "p",
            "a",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "r",
            "n",
            "t",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "i",
            "a",
            "h",
            "l",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The feeling of being joyful and glad.",
        "answer": "happy"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "l",
            "a",
            "g",
            "o",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "o",
            "g",
            "r",
            "o",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "l",
            "i",
            "n",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "c",
            "o",
            "l",
            "c",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "o",
            "s",
            "o",
            "o",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "s",
            "e",
            "i",
            "t",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "It hangs on the wall and tells you the time.",
        "answer": "clock"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "r",
            "t",
            "h",
            "o",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "t",
            "l",
            "t",
            "f",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "r",
            "u",
            "y",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "o",
            "o",
            "i",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "r",
            "x",
            "i",
            "m",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "o",
            "n",
            "e",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You use this body part to speak and eat.",
        "answer": "mouth"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 12,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "t",
            "o",
            "w",
            "i",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "r",
            "e",
            "i",
            "h",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "v",
            "e",
            "o",
            "y",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "w",
            "r",
            "r",
            "o",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "t",
            "t",
            "n",
            "a",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "i",
            "a",
            "t",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You walk up these to reach the next floor.",
        "answer": "stairs"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "u",
            "o",
            "s",
            "t",
            "o",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "o",
            "o",
            "e",
            "e",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "s",
            "a",
            "i",
            "w",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "s",
            "g",
            "r",
            "l",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "m",
            "l",
            "e",
            "l",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "n",
            "e",
            "i",
            "r",
            "f"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A person you like, trust, and enjoy playing with.",
        "answer": "friend"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "o",
            "p",
            "a",
            "t",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "e",
            "i",
            "h",
            "m",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "j",
            "e",
            "a",
            "n",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "k",
            "r",
            "a",
            "h",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "i",
            "h",
            "o",
            "r",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "t",
            "u",
            "i",
            "a",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A big fish in the ocean with sharp teeth.",
        "answer": "shark"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "title": "Level 10 \u2014 Grandmaster",
    "timeLimit": 70,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 1012,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "a",
            "i",
            "i",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "l",
            "s",
            "e",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "x",
            "e",
            "d",
            "i",
            "s",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "a",
            "t",
            "n",
            "n",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "s",
            "s",
            "v",
            "a",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "f",
            "h",
            "s",
            "n",
            "c"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am made of wax and give light when burned.",
        "answer": "candle"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "s",
            "a",
            "a",
            "e",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "p",
            "l",
            "u",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "s",
            "r",
            "t",
            "d",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "x",
            "t",
            "l",
            "s",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "e",
            "e",
            "t",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "o",
            "t",
            "i",
            "t",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am yellow, made from milk, and spread on toast.",
        "answer": "butter"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "t",
            "d",
            "d",
            "c",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "y",
            "l",
            "e",
            "a",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "l",
            "l",
            "s",
            "o",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "a",
            "k",
            "u",
            "t",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "t",
            "o",
            "n",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "n",
            "o",
            "e",
            "s",
            "y"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You carry groceries or a picnic in this.",
        "answer": "basket"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "k",
            "o",
            "e",
            "h",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "i",
            "f",
            "i",
            "i",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "t",
            "n",
            "a",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "t",
            "e",
            "r",
            "l",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "m",
            "l",
            "o",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "n",
            "o",
            "w",
            "c",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A very young cat.",
        "answer": "kitten"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "c",
            "d",
            "d",
            "c",
            "r",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "s",
            "u",
            "p",
            "a",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "n",
            "n",
            "n",
            "b",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "r",
            "t",
            "t",
            "b",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "e",
            "u",
            "o",
            "i",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "h",
            "m",
            "p",
            "t",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have long ears, a fluffy tail, and I hop.",
        "answer": "rabbit"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "t",
            "c",
            "f",
            "a",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "v",
            "i",
            "m",
            "u",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "h",
            "p",
            "r",
            "f",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "l",
            "t",
            "h",
            "n",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "l",
            "n",
            "h",
            "n",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "r",
            "o",
            "i",
            "n",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I move slowly and carry a hard shell on my back.",
        "answer": "turtle"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "l",
            "l",
            "r",
            "o",
            "o",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "i",
            "n",
            "e",
            "a",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "f",
            "c",
            "r",
            "t",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "d",
            "r",
            "n",
            "i",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "n",
            "f",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "u",
            "i",
            "n",
            "m",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A colorful bird that can copy human speech.",
        "answer": "parrot"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 14,
        "grid": [
          [
            "u",
            "o",
            "h",
            "n",
            "r",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "r",
            "h",
            "n",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "m",
            "n",
            "o",
            "g",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "h",
            "i",
            "a",
            "z",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "r",
            "a",
            "z",
            "i",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "p",
            "r",
            "r",
            "a",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A reptile with scales that loves the sun.",
        "answer": "lizard"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "n",
            "e",
            "i",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "s",
            "n",
            "r",
            "o",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "n",
            "t",
            "i",
            "m",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "a",
            "o",
            "t",
            "g",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "k",
            "n",
            "q",
            "o",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "o",
            "o",
            "f",
            "g"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have no legs and I slither on the ground.",
        "answer": "snake"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "o",
            "a",
            "a",
            "r",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "e",
            "o",
            "o",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "p",
            "p",
            "u",
            "p",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "t",
            "i",
            "n",
            "d",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "r",
            "t",
            "n",
            "r",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "h",
            "c",
            "t",
            "e",
            "g"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A very young dog.",
        "answer": "puppy"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "title": "Level 11 \u2014 Challenger",
    "timeLimit": 65,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 1148,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "b",
            "b",
            "u",
            "p",
            "x"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "i",
            "s",
            "x",
            "a",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "o",
            "n",
            "d",
            "s",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "h",
            "h",
            "m",
            "n",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "u",
            "n",
            "c",
            "o",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "n",
            "y",
            "r",
            "e",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have no mouth, but I always reply when you call me.",
        "answer": "echo"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "t",
            "t",
            "e",
            "t",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "e",
            "i",
            "w",
            "r",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "i",
            "p",
            "d",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "a",
            "s",
            "a",
            "i",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "a",
            "i",
            "m",
            "a",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "e",
            "v",
            "s",
            "e",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have cities, but no houses. I have mountains, but no trees.",
        "answer": "map"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "y",
            "a",
            "g",
            "r",
            "g",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "o",
            "d",
            "t",
            "p",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "r",
            "g",
            "k",
            "m",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "a",
            "o",
            "a",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "s",
            "i",
            "u",
            "t",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "u",
            "t",
            "e",
            "s",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I appear once in a minute, twice in a moment, but never in a thousand years.",
        "answer": "stamp"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "d",
            "g",
            "r",
            "a",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "s",
            "l",
            "a",
            "r",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "l",
            "o",
            "u",
            "t",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "h",
            "v",
            "i",
            "c",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "b",
            "e",
            "h",
            "t",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "w",
            "n",
            "h",
            "h",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have a thumb and four fingers, but I am not alive.",
        "answer": "glove"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "t",
            "u",
            "s",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "i",
            "s",
            "s",
            "g",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "a",
            "i",
            "n",
            "y",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "t",
            "o",
            "i",
            "s",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "p",
            "r",
            "a",
            "o",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "s",
            "l",
            "i",
            "f"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am full of holes but still hold water.",
        "answer": "sponge"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "d",
            "h",
            "f",
            "p",
            "l",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "n",
            "o",
            "i",
            "n",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "a",
            "o",
            "e",
            "o",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "s",
            "l",
            "o",
            "n",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "x",
            "i",
            "l",
            "t",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "s",
            "p",
            "e",
            "i",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have layers like an ogre, and I make you cry.",
        "answer": "onion"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "s",
            "s",
            "o",
            "o",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "s",
            "n",
            "t",
            "r",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "w",
            "i",
            "i",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "t",
            "b",
            "w",
            "l",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "i",
            "o",
            "o",
            "o",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "e",
            "i",
            "i",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I get wetter the more I dry.",
        "answer": "towel"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "t",
            "c",
            "d",
            "s",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "n",
            "n",
            "r",
            "e",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "r",
            "a",
            "r",
            "i",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "x",
            "r",
            "t",
            "i",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "u",
            "y",
            "i",
            "p",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "c",
            "p",
            "n",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have many keys but cannot open a single lock.",
        "answer": "piano"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "l",
            "c",
            "k",
            "l",
            "b",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "h",
            "e",
            "j",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "i",
            "t",
            "r",
            "s",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "c",
            "h",
            "t",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "o",
            "t",
            "n",
            "a",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "a",
            "k",
            "c",
            "o",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am a place where you keep your money safe.",
        "answer": "bank"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "o",
            "a",
            "r",
            "c",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "h",
            "i",
            "e",
            "s",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "i",
            "i",
            "e",
            "n",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "d",
            "n",
            "l",
            "s",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "o",
            "m",
            "b",
            "w",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "e",
            "p",
            "n",
            "m",
            "d"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have teeth but I cannot eat.",
        "answer": "comb"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "title": "Level 12 \u2014 Brain Teasers",
    "timeLimit": 60,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 1288,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "i",
            "g",
            "a",
            "s",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "o",
            "n",
            "e",
            "e",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "i",
            "q",
            "e",
            "m",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "s",
            "d",
            "m",
            "e",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "l",
            "d",
            "h",
            "h",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "w",
            "l",
            "s",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have an eye but I cannot see a thing.",
        "answer": "needle"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "d",
            "o",
            "e",
            "e",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "t",
            "e",
            "i",
            "u",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "h",
            "d",
            "t",
            "i",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "u",
            "i",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "r",
            "t",
            "a",
            "e",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "k",
            "e",
            "m",
            "m"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am always coming, but I never arrive.",
        "answer": "future"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "e",
            "s",
            "n",
            "g",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "e",
            "r",
            "c",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "y",
            "r",
            "a",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "f",
            "l",
            "h",
            "y",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "i",
            "o",
            "o",
            "d",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "a",
            "n",
            "g",
            "e",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "If you say my name, you break me.",
        "answer": "secret"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "u",
            "u",
            "e",
            "s",
            "o",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "g",
            "t",
            "n",
            "t",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "r",
            "a",
            "a",
            "n",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "t",
            "t",
            "a",
            "l",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "o",
            "a",
            "h",
            "t",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "i",
            "i",
            "h",
            "e",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have eyes but cannot see, skin but cannot feel.",
        "answer": "potato"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "g",
            "t",
            "l",
            "s",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "e",
            "a",
            "f",
            "o",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "i",
            "n",
            "t",
            "m",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "s",
            "t",
            "o",
            "z",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "l",
            "r",
            "e",
            "o",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "a",
            "i",
            "l",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have a neck but I do not have a head.",
        "answer": "bottle"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "d",
            "t",
            "p",
            "i",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "c",
            "t",
            "a",
            "a",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "d",
            "n",
            "r",
            "p",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "y",
            "k",
            "h",
            "s",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "e",
            "n",
            "n",
            "m",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "e",
            "s",
            "e",
            "t",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A place with many stalls where people buy and sell.",
        "answer": "market"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "w",
            "r",
            "c",
            "r",
            "i",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "o",
            "b",
            "m",
            "d",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "c",
            "e",
            "e",
            "h",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "e",
            "a",
            "p",
            "o",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "x",
            "o",
            "f",
            "d",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "c",
            "o",
            "e",
            "h",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I start with T, end with T, and am filled with T.",
        "answer": "teapot"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "s",
            "p",
            "h",
            "o",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "u",
            "i",
            "u",
            "e",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "s",
            "l",
            "i",
            "i",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "h",
            "l",
            "u",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "e",
            "o",
            "a",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "n",
            "w",
            "r",
            "n",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have feathers but cannot fly. You sleep on me.",
        "answer": "pillow"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "h",
            "f",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "g",
            "d",
            "n",
            "e",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "a",
            "n",
            "e",
            "m",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "t",
            "t",
            "a",
            "d",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "a",
            "t",
            "o",
            "r",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "t",
            "n",
            "e",
            "i",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am both a fruit and a color.",
        "answer": "orange"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "o",
            "e",
            "e",
            "a",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "a",
            "b",
            "n",
            "p",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "e",
            "w",
            "s",
            "i",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "z",
            "e",
            "s",
            "e",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "f",
            "e",
            "h",
            "x",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "n",
            "a",
            "h",
            "t",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "You aim for me when you throw a dart.",
        "answer": "target"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "title": "Level 13 \u2014 Enigma",
    "timeLimit": 60,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 1428,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "b",
            "e",
            "f",
            "n",
            "r",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "r",
            "e",
            "a",
            "t",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "u",
            "d",
            "e",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "m",
            "t",
            "w",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "s",
            "e",
            "l",
            "r",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "i",
            "e",
            "s",
            "d"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am lighter than a feather, but even the strongest man cannot hold me for long.",
        "answer": "breath"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "y",
            "i",
            "h",
            "a",
            "n",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "r",
            "a",
            "s",
            "n",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "s",
            "o",
            "e",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "t",
            "m",
            "m",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "e",
            "o",
            "t",
            "e",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "i",
            "g",
            "a",
            "d",
            "m"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I can be lost, found, or shared, but I have no physical form.",
        "answer": "memory"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "o",
            "r",
            "n",
            "o",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "o",
            "r",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "h",
            "d",
            "a",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "m",
            "c",
            "r",
            "g",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "r",
            "n",
            "s",
            "u",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "u",
            "a",
            "f",
            "t",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "To use me, you must throw me away. When you are done, you bring me back.",
        "answer": "anchor"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "h",
            "r",
            "j",
            "d",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "m",
            "s",
            "r",
            "s",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "r",
            "h",
            "s",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "o",
            "d",
            "a",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "r",
            "i",
            "r",
            "l",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "t",
            "h",
            "c",
            "h",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "What 5-letter word becomes shorter when you add two letters to it?",
        "answer": "short"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "t",
            "r",
            "l",
            "g",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "s",
            "h",
            "n",
            "n",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "t",
            "o",
            "m",
            "o",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "o",
            "u",
            "n",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "s",
            "t",
            "t",
            "e",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "v",
            "t",
            "d",
            "n",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Which word is written incorrectly in every dictionary?",
        "answer": "wrong"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "a",
            "a",
            "k",
            "e",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "e",
            "p",
            "p",
            "e",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "g",
            "p",
            "h",
            "n",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "w",
            "l",
            "n",
            "p",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "y",
            "a",
            "w",
            "f",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "i",
            "f",
            "s",
            "e",
            "m"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have a hot temper, I am often ground, and I make you sneeze.",
        "answer": "pepper"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "b",
            "n",
            "a",
            "o",
            "o",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "u",
            "n",
            "u",
            "i",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "s",
            "t",
            "o",
            "r",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "i",
            "h",
            "t",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "d",
            "t",
            "m",
            "o",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "b",
            "o",
            "e",
            "l",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I hold things together but have no arms. I have holes but cannot see.",
        "answer": "button"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "c",
            "s",
            "a",
            "t",
            "n",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "s",
            "n",
            "a",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "t",
            "l",
            "e",
            "c",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "e",
            "t",
            "r",
            "s",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "t",
            "t",
            "l",
            "a",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "u",
            "g",
            "c",
            "s",
            "g"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have a clove but no spice, layers but no clothes.",
        "answer": "garlic"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "c",
            "u",
            "a",
            "o",
            "r",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "h",
            "r",
            "e",
            "i",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "o",
            "o",
            "y",
            "c",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "n",
            "e",
            "i",
            "i",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "a",
            "h",
            "s",
            "c",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "e",
            "n",
            "e",
            "e",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I can be hard to make, but I am necessary to move forward.",
        "answer": "choice"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "u",
            "s",
            "e",
            "w",
            "k",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "r",
            "t",
            "r",
            "i",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "l",
            "t",
            "c",
            "o",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "a",
            "o",
            "r",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "e",
            "t",
            "t",
            "e",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "a",
            "h",
            "e",
            "o",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I can be a number, or I can be mailed to a friend.",
        "answer": "letter"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "title": "Level 14 \u2014 Mind Games",
    "timeLimit": 60,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 1568,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "r",
            "h",
            "t",
            "y",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "c",
            "c",
            "i",
            "h",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "i",
            "i",
            "a",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "l",
            "y",
            "v",
            "u",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "n",
            "k",
            "e",
            "d",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "y",
            "u",
            "i",
            "d",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Everyone gives it, but few people take it.",
        "answer": "advice"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "b",
            "i",
            "d",
            "o",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "m",
            "a",
            "s",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "p",
            "a",
            "n",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "a",
            "n",
            "e",
            "h",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "u",
            "a",
            "e",
            "m",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "u",
            "s",
            "g",
            "n",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have a light at the end, but I am dark inside.",
        "answer": "tunnel"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "i",
            "e",
            "i",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "c",
            "e",
            "l",
            "r",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "h",
            "n",
            "z",
            "p",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "s",
            "t",
            "z",
            "u",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "c",
            "g",
            "u",
            "t",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "s",
            "l",
            "p",
            "h",
            "d"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "If you lose just one of my pieces, I cannot be solved.",
        "answer": "puzzle"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "k",
            "o",
            "e",
            "i",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "u",
            "c",
            "f",
            "l",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "s",
            "r",
            "r",
            "d",
            "z"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "l",
            "a",
            "n",
            "d",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "g",
            "c",
            "a",
            "i",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "t",
            "p",
            "f",
            "r",
            "l"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I can be cracked, made, told, and played.",
        "answer": "riddle"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "l",
            "c",
            "a",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "d",
            "n",
            "h",
            "o",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "t",
            "e",
            "a",
            "m",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "f",
            "a",
            "n",
            "a",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "b",
            "e",
            "g",
            "c",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "s",
            "e",
            "e",
            "f",
            "y"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "People often fear me, but without me, you cannot grow.",
        "answer": "change"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "b",
            "a",
            "h",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "r",
            "t",
            "l",
            "a",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "l",
            "s",
            "o",
            "h",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "a",
            "s",
            "l",
            "t",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "i",
            "d",
            "w",
            "r",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "i",
            "t",
            "v",
            "i",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am easy to start, hard to break, and I define you.",
        "answer": "habit"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "u",
            "s",
            "h",
            "m",
            "w"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "t",
            "s",
            "t",
            "a",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "s",
            "g",
            "c",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "i",
            "o",
            "r",
            "c",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "e",
            "n",
            "h",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "p",
            "r",
            "i",
            "h",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have a head but no face. I start a fire when struck.",
        "answer": "match"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "i",
            "r",
            "t",
            "o",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "s",
            "o",
            "v",
            "e",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "m",
            "r",
            "x",
            "t",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "k",
            "r",
            "t",
            "i",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "r",
            "e",
            "i",
            "e",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "r",
            "o",
            "s",
            "p",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am a mistake, a bug, or a blunder.",
        "answer": "error"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "n",
            "y",
            "h",
            "u",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "h",
            "c",
            "r",
            "o",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "c",
            "l",
            "e",
            "e",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "u",
            "o",
            "t",
            "c",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "m",
            "t",
            "n",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "h",
            "p",
            "d",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "One of the five senses; you use your hands for this.",
        "answer": "touch"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 15,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "p",
            "s",
            "o",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "x",
            "e",
            "a",
            "h",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "t",
            "s",
            "o",
            "o",
            "j"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "m",
            "n",
            "h",
            "h",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "t",
            "e",
            "d",
            "e",
            "w"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "g",
            "s",
            "r",
            "e",
            "b"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am common, but many people seem to lack me.",
        "answer": "sense"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "title": "Level 15 \u2014 Abstract Logic",
    "timeLimit": 75,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 1708,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 20,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "r",
            "u",
            "h",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "a",
            "f",
            "o",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "t",
            "b",
            "i",
            "s",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "s",
            "n",
            "o",
            "i",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "e",
            "a",
            "e",
            "w",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "z",
            "h",
            "f",
            "c",
            "t",
            "u"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The highest point reached by a celestial body; a peak directly above.",
        "answer": "zenith"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 20,
        "grid": [
          [
            "v",
            "q",
            "e",
            "u",
            "h",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "o",
            "s",
            "e",
            "e",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "n",
            "r",
            "o",
            "i",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "q",
            "t",
            "t",
            "n",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "i",
            "o",
            "r",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "n",
            "o",
            "h",
            "g",
            "x"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A whirling mass of fluid or air; a chaotic draw.",
        "answer": "vortex"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 20,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "n",
            "n",
            "i",
            "e",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "o",
            "n",
            "e",
            "i",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "l",
            "o",
            "p",
            "h",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "s",
            "h",
            "i",
            "w",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "e",
            "l",
            "u",
            "p",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "t",
            "t",
            "h",
            "o",
            "f"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A zero, or a secret code to crack.",
        "answer": "cipher"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 20,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "p",
            "f",
            "t",
            "t",
            "q"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "r",
            "y",
            "r",
            "u",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "r",
            "c",
            "a",
            "l",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "l",
            "s",
            "o",
            "v",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "a",
            "e",
            "n",
            "h",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "w",
            "o",
            "x",
            "b",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A massive celestial object emitting exceptionally large amounts of energy.",
        "answer": "quasar"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 20,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "h",
            "a",
            "p",
            "o",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "h",
            "c",
            "m",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "i",
            "c",
            "a",
            "i",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "s",
            "o",
            "e",
            "i",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "o",
            "a",
            "l",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "f",
            "r",
            "b",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have no voice, yet I repeat every word you say.",
        "answer": "echo"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 20,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "f",
            "i",
            "n",
            "m",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "f",
            "a",
            "h",
            "i",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "t",
            "o",
            "e",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "a",
            "o",
            "t",
            "t",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "a",
            "y",
            "u",
            "h",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "x",
            "i",
            "l",
            "e",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The shape of your DNA; a 3D spiral curve.",
        "answer": "helix"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 20,
        "grid": [
          [
            "f",
            "e",
            "k",
            "t",
            "t",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "s",
            "s",
            "u",
            "v",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "p",
            "s",
            "c",
            "m",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "t",
            "y",
            "m",
            "s",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "l",
            "b",
            "n",
            "a",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "o",
            "a",
            "e",
            "s",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A bottomless pit; gaze into it and it gazes back.",
        "answer": "abyss"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 20,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "s",
            "a",
            "u",
            "o",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "h",
            "i",
            "t",
            "o",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "e",
            "t",
            "x",
            "a",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "p",
            "l",
            "i",
            "s",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "a",
            "r",
            "c",
            "r",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "x",
            "r",
            "r",
            "t",
            "e",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Continuous change, or a substance used in soldering.",
        "answer": "flux"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 20,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "t",
            "y",
            "m",
            "h",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "e",
            "i",
            "h",
            "f",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "o",
            "d",
            "e",
            "m",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "a",
            "i",
            "t",
            "n",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "t",
            "t",
            "o",
            "l",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "d",
            "a",
            "p",
            "c",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A traditional story explaining natural or social phenomenon.",
        "answer": "myth"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 20,
        "grid": [
          [
            "d",
            "j",
            "l",
            "o",
            "e",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "t",
            "o",
            "n",
            "e",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "r",
            "z",
            "h",
            "f",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "o",
            "o",
            "n",
            "b",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "o",
            "n",
            "c",
            "w",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "a",
            "e",
            "i",
            "a",
            "f"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A pale blue gas; a layer that protects Earth.",
        "answer": "ozone"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "title": "Level 16 \u2014 Cosmic Void",
    "timeLimit": 80,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 1898,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 25,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "e",
            "y",
            "c",
            "h",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "m",
            "x",
            "o",
            "w",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "l",
            "a",
            "s",
            "n",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "t",
            "l",
            "g",
            "n",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "l",
            "a",
            "o",
            "f",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "g",
            "v",
            "a",
            "p"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A massive system of stars, stellar remnants, gas, and dust.",
        "answer": "galaxy"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 25,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "o",
            "e",
            "l",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "e",
            "f",
            "t",
            "o",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "d",
            "i",
            "m",
            "l",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "t",
            "e",
            "t",
            "t",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "n",
            "p",
            "a",
            "q"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "t",
            "e",
            "s",
            "o",
            "v"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A celestial object with a tail of gas and dust.",
        "answer": "comet"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 25,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "n",
            "t",
            "h",
            "a",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "s",
            "t",
            "e",
            "c",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "s",
            "f",
            "r",
            "c",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "x",
            "f",
            "a",
            "e",
            "f",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "r",
            "s",
            "x",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "l",
            "i",
            "s",
            "b",
            "m"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A 'shooting star' that enters Earth's atmosphere.",
        "answer": "meteor"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 25,
        "grid": [
          [
            "l",
            "l",
            "i",
            "a",
            "f",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "e",
            "s",
            "d",
            "l",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "e",
            "g",
            "u",
            "h",
            "j"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "b",
            "r",
            "o",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "h",
            "h",
            "p",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "r",
            "e",
            "o",
            "l",
            "b"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A giant cloud of dust and gas in space.",
        "answer": "nebula"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 25,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "n",
            "c",
            "e",
            "i",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "m",
            "d",
            "b",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "n",
            "a",
            "e",
            "t",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "y",
            "s",
            "i",
            "g",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "r",
            "a",
            "w",
            "d",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "o",
            "k",
            "n",
            "l",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A small star of relatively high density.",
        "answer": "dwarf"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 25,
        "grid": [
          [
            "l",
            "p",
            "s",
            "h",
            "e",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "u",
            "p",
            "o",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "g",
            "b",
            "m",
            "t",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "t",
            "n",
            "a",
            "i",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "a",
            "a",
            "a",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "p",
            "a",
            "e",
            "r",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A star of great size and luminosity.",
        "answer": "giant"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 25,
        "grid": [
          [
            "p",
            "u",
            "l",
            "s",
            "a",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "f",
            "r",
            "d",
            "c",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "o",
            "s",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "s",
            "h",
            "h",
            "m",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "s",
            "g",
            "t",
            "d",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "d",
            "s",
            "s",
            "n",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A rotating neutron star that emits a beam of electromagnetic radiation.",
        "answer": "pulsar"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 25,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "n",
            "a",
            "i",
            "i",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "c",
            "n",
            "t",
            "k",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "x",
            "n",
            "t",
            "u",
            "c",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "u",
            "n",
            "a",
            "l",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "w",
            "l",
            "t",
            "e",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "b",
            "o",
            "w",
            "e",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A region of space where gravity prevents even light from escaping.",
        "answer": "black"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 25,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "r",
            "c",
            "p",
            "e",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "o",
            "f",
            "u",
            "h",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "s",
            "w",
            "a",
            "t",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "t",
            "e",
            "c",
            "i",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "r",
            "h",
            "t",
            "t",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "d",
            "i",
            "a",
            "a",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Relating to the sun.",
        "answer": "solar"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 25,
        "grid": [
          [
            "v",
            "y",
            "n",
            "o",
            "t",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "s",
            "r",
            "d",
            "u",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "n",
            "t",
            "u",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "u",
            "n",
            "a",
            "r",
            "z"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "l",
            "h",
            "n",
            "u",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "e",
            "a",
            "e",
            "m",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Relating to the moon.",
        "answer": "lunar"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "title": "Level 17 \u2014 Digital Realm",
    "timeLimit": 80,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 2138,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 30,
        "grid": [
          [
            "l",
            "o",
            "e",
            "g",
            "h",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "n",
            "i",
            "t",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "a",
            "l",
            "o",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "s",
            "x",
            "o",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "i",
            "r",
            "m",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "p",
            "a",
            "o",
            "r",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A tiny square of light; millions combine to form your view.",
        "answer": "pixel"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 30,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "r",
            "c",
            "a",
            "h",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "p",
            "a",
            "i",
            "t",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "e",
            "c",
            "a",
            "e",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "o",
            "h",
            "i",
            "e",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "a",
            "e",
            "w",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "p",
            "l",
            "h",
            "h",
            "l"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Hidden storage used to speed up retrieval.",
        "answer": "cache"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 30,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "t",
            "t",
            "o",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "t",
            "h",
            "m",
            "i",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "o",
            "s",
            "c",
            "r",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "u",
            "m",
            "t",
            "y",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "t",
            "i",
            "e",
            "u",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "a",
            "e",
            "a",
            "s",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A microscopic invader, whether biological or digital.",
        "answer": "virus"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 30,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "h",
            "n",
            "n",
            "e",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "i",
            "g",
            "o",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "s",
            "a",
            "t",
            "e",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "i",
            "a",
            "f",
            "f",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "g",
            "u",
            "p",
            "f",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "t",
            "n",
            "s",
            "d",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The gateway ritual to access a secure system.",
        "answer": "login"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 30,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "e",
            "o",
            "o",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "e",
            "u",
            "n",
            "l",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "n",
            "o",
            "c",
            "n",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "d",
            "e",
            "w",
            "a",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "h",
            "o",
            "o",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "i",
            "e",
            "w",
            "i",
            "c"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A distinct point of connection in a network graph.",
        "answer": "node"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 30,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "e",
            "s",
            "t",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "z",
            "o",
            "x",
            "a",
            "y",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "l",
            "h",
            "t",
            "n",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "g",
            "e",
            "t",
            "h",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "d",
            "h",
            "a",
            "t",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "c",
            "y",
            "t",
            "o",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Exactly eight bits; a mouthful of data.",
        "answer": "byte"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 30,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "d",
            "w",
            "e",
            "u",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "e",
            "t",
            "i",
            "i",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "y",
            "v",
            "h",
            "n",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "k",
            "t",
            "r",
            "u",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "o",
            "a",
            "f",
            "e",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "d",
            "a",
            "i",
            "n",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I wait for your requests and deliver the data.",
        "answer": "server"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 30,
        "grid": [
          [
            "l",
            "r",
            "o",
            "e",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "d",
            "e",
            "d",
            "i",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "n",
            "u",
            "r",
            "s",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "o",
            "a",
            "o",
            "e",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "i",
            "a",
            "c",
            "l",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "t",
            "t",
            "e",
            "i",
            "c"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I float in the sky, or store your photos remotely.",
        "answer": "cloud"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 30,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "s",
            "i",
            "p",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "r",
            "a",
            "r",
            "r",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "o",
            "t",
            "s",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "x",
            "y",
            "i",
            "r",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "k",
            "d",
            "t",
            "n",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "d",
            "a",
            "n",
            "a",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A substitute; an intermediary acting on your behalf.",
        "answer": "proxy"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 30,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "t",
            "u",
            "b",
            "i",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "f",
            "d",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "h",
            "k",
            "y",
            "c",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "z",
            "t",
            "l",
            "o",
            "v",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "c",
            "f",
            "n",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "l",
            "d",
            "o",
            "i",
            "p"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A coin for the arcade, or a digital proof of ownership.",
        "answer": "token"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "title": "Level 18 \u2014 Ancient Mysteries",
    "timeLimit": 85,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 2428,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 35,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "l",
            "o",
            "f",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "p",
            "o",
            "f",
            "a",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "m",
            "h",
            "m",
            "i",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "i",
            "i",
            "v",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "t",
            "s",
            "s",
            "n",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "t",
            "o",
            "d",
            "p",
            "x"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A mythical creature with the body of a lion and head of a human; a riddler.",
        "answer": "sphinx"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 35,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "e",
            "r",
            "l",
            "h",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "h",
            "t",
            "y",
            "h",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "t",
            "t",
            "a",
            "a",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "e",
            "l",
            "i",
            "c",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "i",
            "e",
            "g",
            "s",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "l",
            "t",
            "n",
            "y",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "An object surviving from an earlier time, often considered holy.",
        "answer": "relic"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 35,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "s",
            "m",
            "n",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "s",
            "c",
            "f",
            "n",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "v",
            "s",
            "h",
            "m",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "n",
            "c",
            "a",
            "t",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "u",
            "e",
            "e",
            "t",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "t",
            "g",
            "i",
            "p",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A priest or medium acting as a channel for divine prophecy.",
        "answer": "oracle"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 35,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "k",
            "p",
            "i",
            "h",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "h",
            "y",
            "w",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "r",
            "a",
            "i",
            "c",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "t",
            "y",
            "h",
            "a",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "d",
            "p",
            "c",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "e",
            "a",
            "w",
            "t",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "An underground room or vault beneath a church, used for burial.",
        "answer": "crypt"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 35,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "t",
            "w",
            "a",
            "t",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "t",
            "o",
            "r",
            "i",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "x",
            "i",
            "h",
            "t",
            "z",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "c",
            "i",
            "m",
            "e",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "n",
            "t",
            "d",
            "l",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "u",
            "u",
            "s",
            "i",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A spirit being, sacred object, or symbol that serves as an emblem of a tribe.",
        "answer": "totem"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 35,
        "grid": [
          [
            "v",
            "p",
            "s",
            "o",
            "v",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "r",
            "e",
            "r",
            "e",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "e",
            "s",
            "m",
            "m",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "o",
            "p",
            "i",
            "o",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "l",
            "i",
            "a",
            "a",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "o",
            "w",
            "a",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A structure reserved for religious or spiritual rituals.",
        "answer": "temple"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 35,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "u",
            "r",
            "c",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "t",
            "a",
            "h",
            "l",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "t",
            "u",
            "n",
            "l",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "o",
            "g",
            "a",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "o",
            "l",
            "o",
            "c",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "o",
            "m",
            "r",
            "p",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A letter of an ancient Germanic alphabet, often used in magic.",
        "answer": "rune"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 35,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "h",
            "q",
            "v",
            "f",
            "w"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "y",
            "a",
            "r",
            "s",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "l",
            "t",
            "n",
            "h",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "o",
            "a",
            "o",
            "d",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "d",
            "h",
            "u",
            "f",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "t",
            "s",
            "i",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "An image or representation of a god used as an object of worship.",
        "answer": "idol"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 35,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "a",
            "l",
            "h",
            "l",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "r",
            "t",
            "s",
            "h",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "o",
            "r",
            "i",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "t",
            "e",
            "n",
            "h",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "b",
            "r",
            "c",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "t",
            "t",
            "o",
            "m",
            "b"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A large vault for burying the dead, often grand.",
        "answer": "tomb"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 35,
        "grid": [
          [
            "c",
            "i",
            "t",
            "e",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "m",
            "a",
            "l",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "z",
            "g",
            "t",
            "i",
            "r",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "r",
            "u",
            "c",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "n",
            "e",
            "i",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "d",
            "i",
            "s",
            "f",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A solemn utterance intended to invoke a supernatural power to inflict harm.",
        "answer": "curse"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "title": "Level 19 \u2014 Elemental Forces",
    "timeLimit": 90,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 2768,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 40,
        "grid": [
          [
            "u",
            "a",
            "t",
            "e",
            "n",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "m",
            "d",
            "i",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "a",
            "o",
            "g",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "t",
            "s",
            "a",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "r",
            "s",
            "o",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "d",
            "j",
            "e",
            "i",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Liquid rock found beneath the Earth's surface.",
        "answer": "magma"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 40,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "c",
            "t",
            "s",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "x",
            "e",
            "h",
            "i",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "r",
            "u",
            "i",
            "v",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "e",
            "t",
            "l",
            "m",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "n",
            "r",
            "o",
            "s",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "d",
            "l",
            "v",
            "t",
            "g"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A substance suspended in the air; steam or mist.",
        "answer": "vapor"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 40,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "a",
            "d",
            "i",
            "i",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "o",
            "i",
            "n",
            "n",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "t",
            "l",
            "n",
            "e",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "h",
            "r",
            "s",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "i",
            "f",
            "s",
            "i",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "s",
            "p",
            "h",
            "n",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The rhythmic rising and falling of the sea.",
        "answer": "tide"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 40,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "b",
            "c",
            "i",
            "a",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "h",
            "l",
            "i",
            "e",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "a",
            "h",
            "a",
            "o",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "i",
            "s",
            "l",
            "z",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "l",
            "g",
            "d",
            "h",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "i",
            "o",
            "a",
            "e",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A fiercely burning fire.",
        "answer": "blaze"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 40,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "i",
            "r",
            "e",
            "u",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "g",
            "h",
            "r",
            "o",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "n",
            "e",
            "s",
            "n",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "u",
            "t",
            "t",
            "r",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "q",
            "u",
            "a",
            "k",
            "e",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "i",
            "o",
            "s",
            "l",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A sudden violent shaking of the ground.",
        "answer": "quake"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 40,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "j",
            "y",
            "n",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "a",
            "h",
            "r",
            "n",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "f",
            "o",
            "v",
            "u",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "r",
            "o",
            "d",
            "h",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "i",
            "l",
            "i",
            "a",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "e",
            "n",
            "f",
            "t",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Pellets of frozen rain.",
        "answer": "hail"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 40,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "n",
            "t",
            "i",
            "f",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "t",
            "n",
            "a",
            "f",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "r",
            "a",
            "r",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "e",
            "o",
            "h",
            "d",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "s",
            "r",
            "a",
            "b",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "d",
            "r",
            "u",
            "h",
            "w"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "White ice crystals that form on cold surfaces.",
        "answer": "frost"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 40,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "v",
            "k",
            "t",
            "a",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "i",
            "i",
            "i",
            "t",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "s",
            "t",
            "o",
            "c",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "h",
            "r",
            "b",
            "m",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "m",
            "n",
            "e",
            "e",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "f",
            "y",
            "c",
            "h",
            "b"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A violent disturbance of the atmosphere.",
        "answer": "storm"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 40,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "l",
            "l",
            "e",
            "e",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "q",
            "a",
            "i",
            "y",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "w",
            "t",
            "a",
            "a",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "n",
            "e",
            "s",
            "r",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "b",
            "c",
            "u",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "l",
            "l",
            "a",
            "p",
            "g"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A brief, strong rush of wind.",
        "answer": "gust"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 40,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "w",
            "i",
            "t",
            "i",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "d",
            "r",
            "s",
            "h",
            "z"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "o",
            "h",
            "v",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "a",
            "n",
            "o",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "g",
            "i",
            "e",
            "l",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "n",
            "t",
            "w",
            "f"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "An overflowing of a large amount of water.",
        "answer": "flood"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "title": "Level 20 \u2014 Chemical Lab",
    "timeLimit": 95,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 3158,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 45,
        "grid": [
          [
            "c",
            "n",
            "r",
            "c",
            "r",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "s",
            "w",
            "a",
            "t",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "r",
            "i",
            "s",
            "h",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "t",
            "u",
            "i",
            "j",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "g",
            "h",
            "i",
            "s",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "y",
            "i",
            "o",
            "a",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The fundamental building block of life; atomic number 6.",
        "answer": "carbon"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 45,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "p",
            "p",
            "e",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "a",
            "h",
            "l",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "w",
            "a",
            "r",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "n",
            "e",
            "s",
            "k",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "g",
            "n",
            "m",
            "r",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "a",
            "a",
            "s",
            "f"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The fourth state of matter, found in stars and lightning.",
        "answer": "plasma"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 45,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "r",
            "i",
            "d",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "p",
            "e",
            "n",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "a",
            "d",
            "n",
            "t",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "f",
            "f",
            "a",
            "w",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "o",
            "r",
            "e",
            "r",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "r",
            "w",
            "s",
            "s",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A radioactive, colorless, odorless noble gas.",
        "answer": "radon"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 45,
        "grid": [
          [
            "y",
            "a",
            "t",
            "a",
            "c",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "f",
            "l",
            "t",
            "p",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "i",
            "r",
            "l",
            "l",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "e",
            "t",
            "t",
            "o",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "s",
            "e",
            "n",
            "d",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "v",
            "s",
            "m",
            "a",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A metal made by combining two or more metallic elements.",
        "answer": "alloy"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 45,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "o",
            "n",
            "e",
            "r",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "h",
            "t",
            "i",
            "d",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "r",
            "s",
            "i",
            "o",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "x",
            "o",
            "n",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "o",
            "m",
            "g",
            "n",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "u",
            "d",
            "e",
            "s",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A chemical compound that contains at least one oxygen atom.",
        "answer": "oxide"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 45,
        "grid": [
          [
            "y",
            "e",
            "f",
            "d",
            "d",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "n",
            "s",
            "i",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "i",
            "w",
            "r",
            "i",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "x",
            "d",
            "t",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "c",
            "e",
            "b",
            "r",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "s",
            "a",
            "n",
            "n",
            "m"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A gas lighter than air, used in balloons.",
        "answer": "helium"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 45,
        "grid": [
          [
            "w",
            "o",
            "b",
            "o",
            "o",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "h",
            "h",
            "t",
            "a",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "n",
            "t",
            "a",
            "h",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "o",
            "p",
            "p",
            "e",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "e",
            "n",
            "h",
            "i",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "e",
            "i",
            "s",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A reddish-brown metal; a great conductor of electricity.",
        "answer": "copper"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 45,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "t",
            "h",
            "a",
            "e",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "a",
            "o",
            "c",
            "a",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "i",
            "o",
            "i",
            "r",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "n",
            "o",
            "d",
            "t",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "a",
            "b",
            "i",
            "w",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "y",
            "s",
            "c",
            "a",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Having a pH less than 7; sour tasting.",
        "answer": "acidic"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 45,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "r",
            "n",
            "l",
            "t",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "l",
            "o",
            "s",
            "s",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "k",
            "e",
            "o",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "h",
            "w",
            "a",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "w",
            "v",
            "s",
            "l",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "p",
            "s",
            "y",
            "a",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A basic, ionic salt; the opposite of acid.",
        "answer": "alkali"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 45,
        "grid": [
          [
            "l",
            "e",
            "f",
            "n",
            "s",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "e",
            "n",
            "t",
            "a",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "o",
            "o",
            "s",
            "i",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "e",
            "v",
            "l",
            "i",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "a",
            "o",
            "a",
            "o",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "n",
            "e",
            "h",
            "o",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A shiny grey-white metal often used in jewelry.",
        "answer": "silver"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "title": "Level 21 \u2014 Deep Ocean",
    "timeLimit": 95,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 3598,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 50,
        "grid": [
          [
            "c",
            "n",
            "a",
            "i",
            "l",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "t",
            "m",
            "a",
            "s",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "h",
            "r",
            "t",
            "s",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "o",
            "l",
            "o",
            "i",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "o",
            "d",
            "o",
            "o",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "o",
            "h",
            "o",
            "n",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I am a living stone, a builder of reefs.",
        "answer": "coral"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 50,
        "grid": [
          [
            "m",
            "h",
            "h",
            "f",
            "s",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "l",
            "i",
            "h",
            "n",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "b",
            "a",
            "o",
            "i",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "a",
            "b",
            "d",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "x",
            "d",
            "g",
            "s",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "g",
            "o",
            "l",
            "n",
            "d"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I have rows of teeth but no bones.",
        "answer": "shark"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 50,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "p",
            "e",
            "a",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "s",
            "l",
            "i",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "o",
            "t",
            "g",
            "h",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "n",
            "f",
            "h",
            "a",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "b",
            "e",
            "a",
            "v",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "u",
            "o",
            "s",
            "s",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The grass of the sea; I produce oxygen.",
        "answer": "algae"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 50,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "h",
            "i",
            "t",
            "u",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "k",
            "r",
            "i",
            "l",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "n",
            "i",
            "o",
            "i",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "a",
            "t",
            "t",
            "i",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "b",
            "i",
            "h",
            "s",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "m",
            "f",
            "n",
            "o",
            "c"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Tiny giants; the fuel for the largest beast.",
        "answer": "krill"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 50,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "s",
            "r",
            "i",
            "h",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "n",
            "n",
            "o",
            "c",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "t",
            "h",
            "t",
            "n",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "e",
            "e",
            "m",
            "e",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "i",
            "o",
            "n",
            "r",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "n",
            "g",
            "i",
            "t",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The deepest scar on the planet's face.",
        "answer": "trench"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 50,
        "grid": [
          [
            "l",
            "e",
            "n",
            "r",
            "a",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "a",
            "s",
            "t",
            "o",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "h",
            "o",
            "o",
            "i",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "l",
            "s",
            "n",
            "f",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "o",
            "b",
            "o",
            "a",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "t",
            "o",
            "i",
            "r",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A ring of land with a lagoon in its heart.",
        "answer": "atoll"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 50,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "h",
            "f",
            "o",
            "b",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "i",
            "r",
            "q",
            "r",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "l",
            "d",
            "e",
            "i",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "c",
            "t",
            "d",
            "n",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "a",
            "r",
            "s",
            "e",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "d",
            "t",
            "s",
            "u",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Water too salty to drink, too heavy to mix.",
        "answer": "brine"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 50,
        "grid": [
          [
            "p",
            "h",
            "g",
            "o",
            "t",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "l",
            "e",
            "k",
            "e",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "n",
            "h",
            "c",
            "m",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "s",
            "n",
            "n",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "d",
            "r",
            "x",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "s",
            "d",
            "i",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I form forests without wood.",
        "answer": "kelp"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 50,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "t",
            "i",
            "o",
            "w"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "t",
            "o",
            "s",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "m",
            "t",
            "p",
            "i",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "n",
            "t",
            "w",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "u",
            "d",
            "e",
            "n",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "r",
            "g",
            "t",
            "e",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "I see with sound in the crushing dark.",
        "answer": "sonar"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 50,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "s",
            "t",
            "a",
            "s",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "n",
            "i",
            "n",
            "b",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "w",
            "s",
            "u",
            "h",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "k",
            "c",
            "i",
            "m",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "t",
            "o",
            "p",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "e",
            "i",
            "v",
            "i",
            "d"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Self-contained breathing in the deep blue.",
        "answer": "scuba"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "title": "Level 22 \u2014 Neon Future",
    "timeLimit": 95,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 4088,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 55,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "s",
            "n",
            "a",
            "r",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "t",
            "f",
            "i",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "r",
            "u",
            "m",
            "r",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "y",
            "b",
            "o",
            "r",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "n",
            "y",
            "n",
            "h",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "t",
            "k",
            "e",
            "h",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Part flesh, part metal; the ultimate hybrid.",
        "answer": "cyborg"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 55,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "i",
            "t",
            "a",
            "n",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "c",
            "p",
            "o",
            "f",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "o",
            "e",
            "t",
            "g",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "n",
            "r",
            "r",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "s",
            "i",
            "s",
            "h",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "i",
            "p",
            "x",
            "i",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The gas that lights up the rainy city streets.",
        "answer": "neon"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 55,
        "grid": [
          [
            "k",
            "n",
            "i",
            "u",
            "o",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "v",
            "n",
            "o",
            "d",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "r",
            "h",
            "e",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "u",
            "m",
            "r",
            "g",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "t",
            "t",
            "s",
            "o",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "e",
            "c",
            "h",
            "a",
            "w"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Giant machines piloted by humans for combat.",
        "answer": "mecha"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 55,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "a",
            "t",
            "i",
            "d",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "h",
            "a",
            "r",
            "u",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "w",
            "o",
            "m",
            "e",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "n",
            "i",
            "l",
            "i",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "t",
            "h",
            "n",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "f",
            "h",
            "o",
            "u",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A silent observer in the sky; a flying spy.",
        "answer": "drone"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 55,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "l",
            "i",
            "t",
            "a",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "t",
            "s",
            "n",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "t",
            "e",
            "t",
            "i",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "t",
            "r",
            "o",
            "g",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "i",
            "e",
            "y",
            "r",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "x",
            "e",
            "h",
            "v",
            "u",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A virtual world where reality is left behind.",
        "answer": "matrix"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 55,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "i",
            "n",
            "l",
            "k",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "x",
            "c",
            "l",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "f",
            "a",
            "a",
            "y",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "h",
            "i",
            "a",
            "s",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "t",
            "e",
            "e",
            "i",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "g",
            "n",
            "i",
            "n",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "To break into the system and steal the data.",
        "answer": "hack"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 55,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "r",
            "t",
            "g",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "n",
            "i",
            "s",
            "e",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "i",
            "a",
            "y",
            "i",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "f",
            "s",
            "n",
            "s",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "n",
            "e",
            "n",
            "n",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "w",
            "h",
            "i",
            "t",
            "y"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Very small technology; microscopic bots.",
        "answer": "nano"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 55,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "d",
            "l",
            "c",
            "r",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "a",
            "s",
            "o",
            "a",
            "j"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "u",
            "a",
            "h",
            "o",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "r",
            "a",
            "y",
            "s",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "u",
            "l",
            "l",
            "m",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "s",
            "l",
            "e",
            "i",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "It's not real, but it feels real.",
        "answer": "null"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 55,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "n",
            "n",
            "r",
            "e",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "r",
            "t",
            "n",
            "d",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "r",
            "e",
            "s",
            "a",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "t",
            "e",
            "o",
            "r",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "u",
            "l",
            "o",
            "t",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "f",
            "y",
            "t",
            "s",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A concentrated beam of light, often a weapon.",
        "answer": "laser"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 55,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "l",
            "i",
            "n",
            "y",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "s",
            "n",
            "s",
            "m",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "y",
            "l",
            "f",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "n",
            "e",
            "h",
            "f",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "t",
            "j",
            "u",
            "h",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "h",
            "x",
            "i",
            "e",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Artificial or robotic; not natural.",
        "answer": "synth"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "title": "Level 23 \u2014 Wasteland",
    "timeLimit": 100,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 4628,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 60,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "r",
            "i",
            "e",
            "n",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "h",
            "p",
            "s",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "r",
            "f",
            "n",
            "t",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "i",
            "l",
            "n",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "u",
            "s",
            "t",
            "r",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "s",
            "e",
            "e",
            "o",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The remains of a destroyed city or building.",
        "answer": "ruins"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 60,
        "grid": [
          [
            "b",
            "c",
            "n",
            "h",
            "n",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "d",
            "h",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "x",
            "c",
            "n",
            "t",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "o",
            "i",
            "n",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "t",
            "u",
            "e",
            "y",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "h",
            "u",
            "i",
            "o",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Poisonous; dangerous to touch or breathe.",
        "answer": "toxic"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 60,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "l",
            "o",
            "t",
            "n",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "r",
            "n",
            "t",
            "m",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "h",
            "i",
            "m",
            "i",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "m",
            "l",
            "n",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "z",
            "t",
            "s",
            "n",
            "h",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "a",
            "r",
            "e",
            "f",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Reverted to a wild state; untamed and savage.",
        "answer": "feral"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 60,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "t",
            "t",
            "t",
            "i",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "r",
            "n",
            "i",
            "j",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "a",
            "l",
            "v",
            "f",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "i",
            "e",
            "p",
            "a",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "i",
            "a",
            "o",
            "n",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "u",
            "u",
            "o",
            "c",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "An underground shelter built for protection.",
        "answer": "bunker"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 60,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "c",
            "a",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "m",
            "e",
            "s",
            "e",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "t",
            "b",
            "h",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "i",
            "p",
            "e",
            "t",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "s",
            "i",
            "s",
            "y",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "a",
            "h",
            "a",
            "h",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The powdery residue left after a fire.",
        "answer": "ashes"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 60,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "i",
            "t",
            "t",
            "t",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "s",
            "c",
            "u",
            "h",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "o",
            "u",
            "m",
            "r",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "h",
            "a",
            "n",
            "h",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "u",
            "g",
            "a",
            "l",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "o",
            "e",
            "t",
            "c"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A contagious bacterial disease that spreads rapidly.",
        "answer": "plague"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 60,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "a",
            "t",
            "i",
            "r",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "h",
            "h",
            "o",
            "y",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "n",
            "w",
            "s",
            "a",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "x",
            "o",
            "r",
            "c",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "c",
            "u",
            "s",
            "e",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "d",
            "b",
            "i",
            "d",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "To rot or decompose gradually.",
        "answer": "decay"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 60,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "p",
            "v",
            "h",
            "v",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "i",
            "h",
            "t",
            "r",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "r",
            "r",
            "b",
            "n",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "d",
            "a",
            "h",
            "e",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "n",
            "a",
            "t",
            "u",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "p",
            "e",
            "i",
            "o",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "An organism with genetic changes, often from radiation.",
        "answer": "mutant"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 60,
        "grid": [
          [
            "b",
            "a",
            "r",
            "r",
            "e",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "y",
            "d",
            "h",
            "d",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "e",
            "a",
            "u",
            "h",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "l",
            "s",
            "l",
            "c",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "s",
            "j",
            "i",
            "t",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "d",
            "a",
            "w",
            "u"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Land too poor to produce any vegetation; empty.",
        "answer": "barren"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 60,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "m",
            "a",
            "n",
            "c",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "h",
            "n",
            "t",
            "s",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "t",
            "s",
            "v",
            "i",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "h",
            "i",
            "t",
            "k",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "h",
            "c",
            "s",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "o",
            "o",
            "m",
            "i",
            "u"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A terrible fate; death or destruction.",
        "answer": "doom"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "title": "Level 24 \u2014 Temporal Rift",
    "timeLimit": 100,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 5218,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 65,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "m",
            "t",
            "y",
            "g",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "p",
            "s",
            "y",
            "a",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "e",
            "e",
            "t",
            "s",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "o",
            "r",
            "i",
            "r",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "o",
            "l",
            "m",
            "l",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "l",
            "n",
            "h",
            "l",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A doorway to another place or time.",
        "answer": "portal"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 65,
        "grid": [
          [
            "p",
            "r",
            "t",
            "r",
            "e",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "m",
            "s",
            "a",
            "o",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "o",
            "t",
            "u",
            "d",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "o",
            "t",
            "p",
            "m",
            "x"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "e",
            "i",
            "i",
            "o",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "t",
            "o",
            "i",
            "n",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A central or focal point; a connection of timelines.",
        "answer": "nexus"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 65,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "s",
            "g",
            "s",
            "r",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "r",
            "t",
            "i",
            "o",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "p",
            "e",
            "s",
            "o",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "c",
            "u",
            "a",
            "a",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "s",
            "t",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "u",
            "n",
            "s",
            "d",
            "c"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A state of inactivity; frozen in time.",
        "answer": "stasis"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 65,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "u",
            "f",
            "r",
            "a",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "i",
            "m",
            "e",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "d",
            "e",
            "s",
            "y",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "i",
            "u",
            "v",
            "h",
            "x"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "a",
            "i",
            "h",
            "n",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "a",
            "i",
            "n",
            "n",
            "d"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Relating to cause and effect.",
        "answer": "causal"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 65,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "r",
            "u",
            "t",
            "u",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "t",
            "r",
            "c",
            "t",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "r",
            "d",
            "t",
            "i",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "r",
            "s",
            "p",
            "c",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "u",
            "i",
            "e",
            "d",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "d",
            "a",
            "s",
            "l",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The time yet to come.",
        "answer": "future"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 65,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "i",
            "f",
            "e",
            "g",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "w",
            "a",
            "l",
            "p",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "e",
            "a",
            "i",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "l",
            "a",
            "r",
            "a",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "k",
            "i",
            "t",
            "p",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "s",
            "d",
            "i",
            "o",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "To distort the shape of space or time.",
        "answer": "warp"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 65,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "i",
            "n",
            "f",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "e",
            "e",
            "o",
            "l",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "h",
            "e",
            "p",
            "t",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "n",
            "l",
            "m",
            "e",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "t",
            "i",
            "e",
            "s",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "i",
            "r",
            "t",
            "c",
            "l"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The speed or pace of a given time.",
        "answer": "tempo"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 65,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "c",
            "o",
            "s",
            "m",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "w",
            "h",
            "s",
            "o",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "h",
            "b",
            "a",
            "m",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "h",
            "e",
            "a",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "a",
            "e",
            "p",
            "n",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "f",
            "e",
            "n",
            "t",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A very brief period of time.",
        "answer": "moment"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 65,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "h",
            "l",
            "i",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "s",
            "a",
            "o",
            "l",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "m",
            "r",
            "o",
            "d",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "n",
            "b",
            "p",
            "e",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "y",
            "e",
            "e",
            "a",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "a",
            "i",
            "e",
            "i",
            "u"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A sequence that repeats itself endlessly.",
        "answer": "loop"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 65,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "m",
            "t",
            "v",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "f",
            "u",
            "i",
            "o",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "a",
            "i",
            "r",
            "l",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "o",
            "a",
            "r",
            "u",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "a",
            "t",
            "t",
            "t",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "a",
            "d",
            "c",
            "t",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A break or separation in continuity.",
        "answer": "rift"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "title": "Level 25 \u2014 Quantum Realm",
    "timeLimit": 105,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 5858,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 70,
        "grid": [
          [
            "p",
            "h",
            "o",
            "t",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "u",
            "p",
            "v",
            "t",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "t",
            "a",
            "a",
            "e",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "c",
            "m",
            "d",
            "e",
            "j"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "n",
            "s",
            "d",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "i",
            "h",
            "h",
            "n",
            "b"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A particle representing a quantum of light.",
        "answer": "photon"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 70,
        "grid": [
          [
            "l",
            "h",
            "h",
            "s",
            "o",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "g",
            "l",
            "u",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "r",
            "p",
            "r",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "o",
            "d",
            "i",
            "t",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "b",
            "p",
            "e",
            "m",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "s",
            "s",
            "u",
            "u",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The messenger particle that acts as 'glue' for the nucleus.",
        "answer": "gluon"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 70,
        "grid": [
          [
            "t",
            "s",
            "a",
            "r",
            "n",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "n",
            "f",
            "a",
            "i",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "d",
            "o",
            "n",
            "a",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "n",
            "d",
            "s",
            "h",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "i",
            "o",
            "d",
            "o",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "m",
            "o",
            "e",
            "e",
            "b"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A subatomic particle, named after Higgs, that carries force.",
        "answer": "boson"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 70,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "s",
            "o",
            "a",
            "n",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "n",
            "w",
            "a",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "n",
            "i",
            "n",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "i",
            "o",
            "i",
            "g",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "m",
            "p",
            "o",
            "i",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "s",
            "e",
            "w",
            "n",
            "m"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Intrinsic angular momentum of a particle.",
        "answer": "spin"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 70,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "y",
            "e",
            "e",
            "s",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "h",
            "r",
            "r",
            "h",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "h",
            "m",
            "s",
            "t",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "l",
            "r",
            "r",
            "f",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "a",
            "t",
            "w",
            "k",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "l",
            "e",
            "i",
            "f",
            "g"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A physical quantity requiring a value for each point in space.",
        "answer": "field"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 70,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "w",
            "n",
            "l",
            "y",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "w",
            "n",
            "e",
            "s",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "a",
            "t",
            "o",
            "v",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "e",
            "t",
            "a",
            "e",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "p",
            "w",
            "t",
            "c",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "y",
            "a",
            "p",
            "r",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "In quantum mechanics, particles also behave like this.",
        "answer": "wave"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 70,
        "grid": [
          [
            "u",
            "t",
            "u",
            "a",
            "a",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "i",
            "p",
            "e",
            "r",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "a",
            "r",
            "i",
            "a",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "w",
            "t",
            "s",
            "f",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "r",
            "t",
            "o",
            "r",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "j",
            "t",
            "r",
            "m",
            "k"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The smallest unit of ordinary matter.",
        "answer": "atom"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 70,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "e",
            "l",
            "f",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "f",
            "n",
            "u",
            "o",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "c",
            "o",
            "r",
            "e",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "r",
            "e",
            "o",
            "e",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "o",
            "i",
            "u",
            "i",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "c",
            "h",
            "t",
            "n",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The extremely dense center of an atom.",
        "answer": "core"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 70,
        "grid": [
          [
            "x",
            "c",
            "c",
            "s",
            "v",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "r",
            "e",
            "r",
            "h",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "u",
            "h",
            "n",
            "r",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "h",
            "f",
            "t",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "l",
            "t",
            "t",
            "d",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "n",
            "p",
            "m",
            "u",
            "j"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A sudden transition of an electron between energy levels.",
        "answer": "jump"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 70,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "t",
            "h",
            "h",
            "o",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "t",
            "s",
            "e",
            "o",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "h",
            "n",
            "l",
            "d",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "a",
            "o",
            "e",
            "f",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "s",
            "e",
            "g",
            "i",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "m",
            "a",
            "e",
            "b",
            "l"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A focused stream of particles or light rays.",
        "answer": "beam"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "title": "Level 26 \u2014 Neural Network",
    "timeLimit": 105,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 6548,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 75,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "u",
            "r",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "r",
            "l",
            "d",
            "a",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "w",
            "o",
            "l",
            "r",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "r",
            "i",
            "a",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "u",
            "o",
            "l",
            "g",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "o",
            "a",
            "h",
            "n",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The fundamental unit of the brain and nervous system.",
        "answer": "neuron"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 75,
        "grid": [
          [
            "v",
            "n",
            "a",
            "o",
            "o",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "m",
            "h",
            "l",
            "a",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "c",
            "a",
            "s",
            "a",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "o",
            "l",
            "t",
            "h",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "h",
            "a",
            "s",
            "s",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "r",
            "o",
            "i",
            "w",
            "x"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The outer layer of the cerebrum; the seat of consciousness.",
        "answer": "cortex"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 75,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "m",
            "t",
            "b",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "e",
            "b",
            "m",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "f",
            "m",
            "d",
            "r",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "k",
            "e",
            "o",
            "i",
            "n",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "s",
            "r",
            "t",
            "n",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "p",
            "y",
            "t",
            "h",
            "j"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The power to retain and recall past experiences.",
        "answer": "memory"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 75,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "o",
            "t",
            "r",
            "h",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "o",
            "r",
            "i",
            "u",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "d",
            "r",
            "r",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "n",
            "i",
            "m",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "l",
            "h",
            "o",
            "p",
            "w"
          ],
          [
            "x",
            "e",
            "l",
            "f",
            "e",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "An involuntary and nearly instantaneous movement.",
        "answer": "reflex"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 75,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "e",
            "f",
            "h",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "t",
            "h",
            "o",
            "h",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "s",
            "n",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "p",
            "n",
            "l",
            "n",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "d",
            "r",
            "e",
            "s",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "y",
            "n",
            "o",
            "h",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Perception through sight, hearing, touch, smell, or taste.",
        "answer": "sense"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 75,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "o",
            "d",
            "s",
            "u",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "n",
            "r",
            "e",
            "t",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "o",
            "e",
            "t",
            "a",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "t",
            "a",
            "e",
            "n",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "m",
            "o",
            "c",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "a",
            "o",
            "c",
            "h",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A series of thoughts and images occurring during sleep.",
        "answer": "dream"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 75,
        "grid": [
          [
            "p",
            "m",
            "e",
            "i",
            "o",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "u",
            "o",
            "d",
            "i",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "m",
            "l",
            "a",
            "x",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "y",
            "r",
            "s",
            "n",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "v",
            "s",
            "g",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "v",
            "o",
            "u",
            "t",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A rhythmic throbbing of arteries; a signal of life.",
        "answer": "pulse"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 75,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "b",
            "o",
            "l",
            "q",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "e",
            "v",
            "i",
            "f",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "t",
            "s",
            "t",
            "q",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "t",
            "a",
            "s",
            "d",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "d",
            "o",
            "t",
            "a",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "i",
            "o",
            "g",
            "a",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A rounded and distinct part of the brain.",
        "answer": "lobe"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 75,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "j",
            "o",
            "v",
            "v",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "a",
            "a",
            "s",
            "i",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "e",
            "a",
            "x",
            "e",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "h",
            "e",
            "d",
            "o",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "s",
            "i",
            "f",
            "a",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "p",
            "f",
            "f",
            "h",
            "f"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The long threadlike part of a nerve cell.",
        "answer": "axon"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 75,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "m",
            "n",
            "n",
            "a",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "c",
            "i",
            "y",
            "e",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "l",
            "r",
            "n",
            "n",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "w",
            "a",
            "r",
            "d",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "b",
            "t",
            "n",
            "t",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "v",
            "o",
            "y",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The element of a person that enables them to be aware.",
        "answer": "mind"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "title": "Level 27 \u2014 Genetic Code",
    "timeLimit": 110,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 7288,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 80,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "t",
            "e",
            "a",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "n",
            "l",
            "e",
            "b",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "m",
            "o",
            "e",
            "t",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "e",
            "n",
            "l",
            "c",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "e",
            "e",
            "i",
            "c",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "w",
            "f",
            "d",
            "f",
            "e",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "An organism or cell produced asexually from one ancestor or stock.",
        "answer": "clone"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 80,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "t",
            "o",
            "x",
            "i",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "y",
            "a",
            "i",
            "r",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "a",
            "e",
            "l",
            "z",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "u",
            "t",
            "e",
            "c",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "p",
            "f",
            "h",
            "l",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "t",
            "o",
            "l",
            "b",
            "c"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A three-dimensional spiral curve; the famous shape of DNA.",
        "answer": "helix"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 80,
        "grid": [
          [
            "r",
            "v",
            "g",
            "a",
            "a",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "r",
            "e",
            "s",
            "b",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "c",
            "n",
            "l",
            "e",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "s",
            "o",
            "k",
            "n",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "j",
            "m",
            "m",
            "t",
            "o",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "f",
            "e",
            "g",
            "d",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The complete set of genes or genetic material present in a cell or organism.",
        "answer": "genome"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 80,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "o",
            "g",
            "r",
            "n",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "a",
            "c",
            "a",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "e",
            "e",
            "m",
            "i",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "s",
            "p",
            "a",
            "e",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "r",
            "f",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "t",
            "e",
            "i",
            "t",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A genetically determined characteristic or quality.",
        "answer": "trait"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 80,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "t",
            "r",
            "c",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "p",
            "e",
            "r",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "v",
            "l",
            "n",
            "t",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "l",
            "s",
            "b",
            "e",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "h",
            "a",
            "e",
            "o",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "n",
            "n",
            "i",
            "u",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The smallest structural and functional unit of an organism.",
        "answer": "cell"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 80,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "l",
            "o",
            "i",
            "t",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "y",
            "d",
            "d",
            "u",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "u",
            "b",
            "s",
            "h",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "l",
            "t",
            "r",
            "c",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "d",
            "e",
            "a",
            "n",
            "i",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "t",
            "a",
            "m",
            "y",
            "d"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The offspring of two plants or animals of different species or varieties.",
        "answer": "hybrid"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 80,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "i",
            "o",
            "k",
            "b",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "d",
            "n",
            "t",
            "c",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "b",
            "a",
            "n",
            "x",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "t",
            "y",
            "p",
            "o",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "a",
            "n",
            "n",
            "t",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "u",
            "n",
            "m",
            "o",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "To become adjusted to new conditions; a mechanism of evolution.",
        "answer": "adapt"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 80,
        "grid": [
          [
            "j",
            "s",
            "s",
            "s",
            "h",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "h",
            "t",
            "s",
            "p",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "j",
            "o",
            "o",
            "a",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "g",
            "r",
            "a",
            "t",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "r",
            "c",
            "t",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "o",
            "w",
            "n",
            "h"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A minute, typically one-celled, reproductive unit capable of giving rise to a new individual.",
        "answer": "spore"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 80,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "e",
            "y",
            "s",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "u",
            "h",
            "r",
            "m",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "s",
            "s",
            "w",
            "a",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "o",
            "n",
            "i",
            "o",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "h",
            "t",
            "r",
            "i",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "e",
            "s",
            "a",
            "b",
            "g"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The four nucleobases (A, C, G, T) that form the 'letters' of DNA.",
        "answer": "bases"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 80,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "u",
            "t",
            "s",
            "n",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "h",
            "d",
            "d",
            "f",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "i",
            "o",
            "r",
            "r",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "t",
            "n",
            "o",
            "n",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "o",
            "o",
            "r",
            "o",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "t",
            "r",
            "a",
            "e",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "One who provides biological tissue or organs to another.",
        "answer": "donor"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "title": "Level 28 \u2014 Nanotech",
    "timeLimit": 110,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 8078,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 85,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "n",
            "e",
            "i",
            "n",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "r",
            "n",
            "t",
            "o",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "l",
            "e",
            "e",
            "e",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "s",
            "o",
            "s",
            "p",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "e",
            "f",
            "s",
            "a",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "s",
            "u",
            "a",
            "s",
            "l"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A device that emits light through optical amplification.",
        "answer": "lasers"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 85,
        "grid": [
          [
            "k",
            "o",
            "t",
            "a",
            "t",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "u",
            "m",
            "c",
            "r",
            "s",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "a",
            "e",
            "k",
            "r",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "m",
            "n",
            "i",
            "m",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "i",
            "v",
            "n",
            "e",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "n",
            "y",
            "t",
            "t",
            "s"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Connects or joins two things together.",
        "answer": "links"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 85,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "a",
            "t",
            "p",
            "o",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "s",
            "o",
            "l",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "o",
            "r",
            "r",
            "m",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "d",
            "m",
            "c",
            "n",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "e",
            "e",
            "r",
            "a",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "a",
            "d",
            "t",
            "v",
            "k"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The positively charged electrode by which electrons leave a device.",
        "answer": "anode"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 85,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "o",
            "t",
            "m",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "i",
            "e",
            "h",
            "i",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "f",
            "d",
            "a",
            "o",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "s",
            "s",
            "x",
            "h",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "v",
            "n",
            "i",
            "n",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "s",
            "m",
            "h",
            "a",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The central or most important part of something.",
        "answer": "core"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 85,
        "grid": [
          [
            "w",
            "s",
            "h",
            "a",
            "g",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "u",
            "r",
            "e",
            "s",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "w",
            "i",
            "e",
            "g",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "i",
            "l",
            "u",
            "r",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "u",
            "o",
            "i",
            "n",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "m",
            "o",
            "h",
            "d",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A protein-rich liquid separated from coagulated blood.",
        "answer": "serum"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 85,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "v",
            "o",
            "e",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "n",
            "n",
            "r",
            "r",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "n",
            "o",
            "n",
            "t",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "d",
            "b",
            "o",
            "x",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "a",
            "i",
            "h",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "e",
            "a",
            "t",
            "i",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "To gradually wear away or destroy.",
        "answer": "erode"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 85,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "m",
            "o",
            "d",
            "r",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "t",
            "o",
            "o",
            "c",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "g",
            "b",
            "g",
            "t",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "a",
            "s",
            "n",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "f",
            "e",
            "u",
            "l",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "e",
            "i",
            "o",
            "c",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "An automated machine, often used in assembly.",
        "answer": "robot"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 85,
        "grid": [
          [
            "e",
            "i",
            "e",
            "y",
            "n",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "o",
            "f",
            "s",
            "r",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "n",
            "e",
            "s",
            "a",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "w",
            "p",
            "s",
            "c",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "d",
            "i",
            "h",
            "i",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "u",
            "e",
            "r",
            "e",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The relative size or extent of something.",
        "answer": "scale"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 85,
        "grid": [
          [
            "m",
            "u",
            "i",
            "l",
            "h",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "v",
            "n",
            "n",
            "i",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "c",
            "h",
            "i",
            "r",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "t",
            "i",
            "o",
            "t",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "t",
            "o",
            "s",
            "b",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "a",
            "u",
            "h",
            "h",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A single quantity regarded as a whole in calculation.",
        "answer": "unit"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "title": "Level 29 \u2014 Geometry Class",
    "timeLimit": 115,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 8833,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 90,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "s",
            "v",
            "a",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "c",
            "t",
            "c",
            "s",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "l",
            "t",
            "s",
            "o",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "r",
            "p",
            "f",
            "e",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "c",
            "c",
            "r",
            "i",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "m",
            "s",
            "i",
            "r",
            "p"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A transparent optical element that refracts light.",
        "answer": "prism"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 90,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "o",
            "s",
            "i",
            "f",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "l",
            "h",
            "n",
            "e",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "e",
            "o",
            "n",
            "o",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "h",
            "i",
            "n",
            "b",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "l",
            "c",
            "t",
            "e",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "t",
            "n",
            "h",
            "i",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The shortest distance between two points.",
        "answer": "line"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 90,
        "grid": [
          [
            "c",
            "h",
            "h",
            "t",
            "u",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "v",
            "n",
            "v",
            "t",
            "o",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "m",
            "e",
            "c",
            "i",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "r",
            "r",
            "o",
            "r",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "d",
            "r",
            "n",
            "m",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "t",
            "e",
            "e",
            "u",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A 3D shape with a circular base tapering to a point.",
        "answer": "cone"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 90,
        "grid": [
          [
            "s",
            "n",
            "r",
            "o",
            "o",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "o",
            "a",
            "e",
            "h",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "h",
            "v",
            "a",
            "c",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "r",
            "t",
            "r",
            "e",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "c",
            "a",
            "r",
            "r",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "l",
            "s",
            "e",
            "e",
            "c"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The origin source; or the mathematical inverse of a power.",
        "answer": "root"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 90,
        "grid": [
          [
            "h",
            "s",
            "o",
            "e",
            "h",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "d",
            "r",
            "i",
            "p",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "l",
            "s",
            "s",
            "s",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "i",
            "c",
            "q",
            "h",
            "x"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "e",
            "y",
            "y",
            "v",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "c",
            "a",
            "u",
            "s",
            "p"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A fixed reference line for the measurement of coordinates.",
        "answer": "axis"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 90,
        "grid": [
          [
            "l",
            "a",
            "a",
            "u",
            "e",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "n",
            "r",
            "r",
            "b",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "r",
            "g",
            "r",
            "u",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "s",
            "m",
            "c",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "c",
            "n",
            "r",
            "h",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "k",
            "c",
            "t",
            "i",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A symmetrical 3D shape contained by six equal squares.",
        "answer": "cube"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 90,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "m",
            "n",
            "h",
            "n",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "e",
            "w",
            "n",
            "s",
            "q"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "a",
            "n",
            "c",
            "o",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "n",
            "o",
            "l",
            "e",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "w",
            "u",
            "o",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "n",
            "c",
            "s",
            "s",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The average of a set of numbers.",
        "answer": "mean"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 90,
        "grid": [
          [
            "u",
            "p",
            "a",
            "r",
            "e",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "a",
            "t",
            "a",
            "c",
            "c"
          ],
          [
            "b",
            "t",
            "f",
            "d",
            "j",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "r",
            "e",
            "i",
            "n",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "s",
            "h",
            "f",
            "a",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "e",
            "r",
            "l",
            "i",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The measurement of a surface or land.",
        "answer": "area"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 90,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "c",
            "t",
            "a",
            "s",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "r",
            "e",
            "a",
            "f",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "e",
            "d",
            "a",
            "t",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "a",
            "s",
            "h",
            "l",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "l",
            "e",
            "l",
            "n",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "i",
            "y",
            "i",
            "o",
            "i"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A type of number that includes both rational and irrational numbers.",
        "answer": "real"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 90,
        "grid": [
          [
            "b",
            "l",
            "h",
            "a",
            "o",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "o",
            "s",
            "p",
            "a",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "c",
            "s",
            "r",
            "r",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "i",
            "r",
            "e",
            "c",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "i",
            "o",
            "n",
            "a",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "l",
            "s",
            "e",
            "o",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A part of the circumference of a circle.",
        "answer": "arc"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "title": "Level 30 \u2014 Theory of Everything",
    "timeLimit": 120,
    "orientation": "6x6",
    "gridSize": 36,
    "unlockCoins": 9723,
    "questions": [
      {
        "q_id": 1,
        "coins": 100,
        "grid": [
          [
            "c",
            "e",
            "i",
            "i",
            "a",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "d",
            "e",
            "e",
            "e",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "l",
            "t",
            "t",
            "n",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "t",
            "l",
            "g",
            "g"
          ],
          [
            "x",
            "a",
            "o",
            "c",
            "w",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "m",
            "y",
            "i",
            "a",
            "e",
            "m"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Physical substance in general that occupies space.",
        "answer": "matter"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 2,
        "coins": 100,
        "grid": [
          [
            "y",
            "l",
            "o",
            "a",
            "t",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "a",
            "a",
            "v",
            "l",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "w",
            "e",
            "t",
            "e",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "c",
            "t",
            "s",
            "e"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "d",
            "n",
            "r",
            "y",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "n",
            "e",
            "d",
            "a",
            "o"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The capacity to do work; power derived from physical or chemical resources.",
        "answer": "energy"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 3,
        "coins": 100,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "f",
            "o",
            "h",
            "s",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "n",
            "i",
            "p",
            "r",
            "a"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "t",
            "a",
            "e",
            "s",
            "w"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "c",
            "t",
            "d",
            "t",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "c",
            "o",
            "o",
            "r",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "o",
            "a",
            "r",
            "h",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The continuous expanse in which things exist and move.",
        "answer": "space"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 4,
        "coins": 100,
        "grid": [
          [
            "i",
            "l",
            "m",
            "t",
            "o",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "a",
            "w",
            "c",
            "o",
            "u"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "e",
            "e",
            "o",
            "v"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "m",
            "e",
            "o",
            "l",
            "h"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "n",
            "i",
            "s",
            "e",
            "w"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "d",
            "a",
            "t",
            "j",
            "t"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The indefinite continued progress of existence.",
        "answer": "time"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 5,
        "coins": 100,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "l",
            "e",
            "y",
            "h",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "i",
            "a",
            "n",
            "e",
            "y"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "g",
            "s",
            "t",
            "h",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "h",
            "l",
            "f",
            "l",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "t",
            "i",
            "t",
            "t",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "y",
            "e",
            "m",
            "t",
            "r"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 1
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Electromagnetic radiation that can be perceived by the human eye.",
        "answer": "light"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 6,
        "coins": 100,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "h",
            "i",
            "e",
            "o",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "i",
            "s",
            "l",
            "m",
            "p"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "o",
            "e",
            "l",
            "t",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "a",
            "l",
            "r",
            "e",
            "t",
            "f"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "g",
            "h",
            "c",
            "o",
            "d"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "u",
            "s",
            "o",
            "e",
            "e"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "Strength or energy as an attribute of physical action or movement.",
        "answer": "force"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 7,
        "coins": 100,
        "grid": [
          [
            "a",
            "s",
            "e",
            "e",
            "d",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "n",
            "t",
            "g",
            "l",
            "d",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "c",
            "e",
            "b",
            "i",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "c",
            "i",
            "c",
            "l",
            "i",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "f",
            "h",
            "e",
            "h",
            "s",
            "o"
          ],
          [
            "h",
            "l",
            "f",
            "o",
            "n",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 0
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 0,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A region in which a particular force is effective.",
        "answer": "field"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 8,
        "coins": 100,
        "grid": [
          [
            "n",
            "h",
            "e",
            "i",
            "a",
            "b"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "n",
            "n",
            "o",
            "o",
            "l"
          ],
          [
            "t",
            "t",
            "s",
            "s",
            "a",
            "m"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "t",
            "s",
            "l",
            "o",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "s",
            "o",
            "o",
            "l",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "i",
            "w",
            "y",
            "h",
            "a"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 5
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 4
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A large body of matter with no definite shape.",
        "answer": "mass"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 9,
        "coins": 100,
        "grid": [
          [
            "o",
            "t",
            "l",
            "u",
            "s",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "v",
            "a",
            "w",
            "g",
            "s"
          ],
          [
            "o",
            "s",
            "r",
            "r",
            "o",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "g",
            "a",
            "l",
            "e",
            "d",
            "k"
          ],
          [
            "s",
            "t",
            "a",
            "s",
            "n",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "y",
            "l",
            "u",
            "i",
            "u",
            "n"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 1,
              "col": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "A disturbance that transfers energy through matter or space.",
        "answer": "wave"
      },
      {
        "q_id": 10,
        "coins": 100,
        "grid": [
          [
            "c",
            "t",
            "t",
            "s",
            "f",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "p",
            "s",
            "a",
            "m",
            "k",
            "i"
          ],
          [
            "e",
            "a",
            "s",
            "a",
            "n",
            "n"
          ],
          [
            "r",
            "s",
            "t",
            "h",
            "l",
            "r"
          ],
          [
            "l",
            "h",
            "o",
            "o",
            "n",
            "t"
          ],
          [
            "i",
            "o",
            "s",
            "m",
            "m",
            "x"
          ]
        ],
        "answerPlacement": {
          "path": [
            {
              "row": 2,
              "col": 1
            },
            {
              "row": 3,
              "col": 2
            },
            {
              "row": 4,
              "col": 3
            },
            {
              "row": 5,
              "col": 4
            }
          ]
        },
        "question": "The basic unit of a chemical element.",
        "answer": "atom"
      }
    ]
  }
]